<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<corpus>
  <document id="/rhodes-beyond-the-obvious-hidden-stories-and-secret-corners/index.html" source="/rhodes-beyond-the-obvious-hidden-stories-and-secret-corners/index.html">
    <title>Rhodes Beyond the Obvious: Hidden Stories and Secret Corners -</title>
    <section name="Rhodes: Uncovering the Island’s Hidden History">Rhodes isn’t just the island of sun and beaches-it’s a place where fascinating secrets of history are waiting to be discovered. Beyond its famous landmarks, the island hides stories and sites that add a whole new dimension to your visit. From Mythology to a Dazzling CityLegend has it that Rhodes emerged from the sea as a gift to the sun god Helios, perhaps explaining the island’s 300 days of sunshine each year. The ancient Rhodians honored Helios with the Colossus of Rhodes-one of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World. Although the statue no longer stands, its spirit is still alive across the island. A City Designed by a VisionaryIn 408 BC, the three ancient cities of Rhodes united to found a new city, designed by the renowned Athenian architect Hippodamus. His revolutionary “Hippodamian” grid plan-straight, intersecting streets-can still be traced today, especially if you visit the Acropolis of Rhodes and Monte Smith Hill. The Medieval Old Town: A Living MuseumThe Old Town of Rhodes, a UNESCO World Heritage Site, is a living, breathing monument. Here, you’ll stroll down the Street of the Knights, marvel at the Palace of the Grand Master, and discover hidden corners where everyday life continues much as it did centuries ago. The Italian Influence That Shaped RhodesDuring the Italian occupation (1912–1943), Rhodes was transformed with impressive new buildings: the Palace of the Grand Master was restored, the famous Kallithea Springs and the Casino of Rhodes (Grande Albergo delle Rose) were built, and the Church of the Annunciation was erected. This Italian architectural flair still gives the city a unique character-just take a walk along Mandraki Harbor and the seafront to see it for yourself. Secrets and Discoveries for the Curious Visitor At the Acropolis of Rhodes and Monte Smith Hill, you can see the remains of the ancient city’s grid plan and the ruins of the Temple of Apollo. In the Old Town, beyond the famous monuments, seek out tiny Byzantine churches, the old Knights’ Hospital (now the Archaeological Museum), and authentic artisan workshops. The Kallithea Springs and the Casino of Rhodes are living examples of the Italian era, open for you to visit and admire up close. Rhodes remains a vibrant crossroads of cultures, where every step reveals a new story-far beyond the typical tourist experience. Rhodes, with its well-kept secrets, invites travelers to experience its history not just through its famous monuments, but through small, authentic moments found in every corner. If you’re looking for something more than just a typical visit, Rhodes will reward you with stories you won’t find in any ordinary travel guide. Ready to discover more hidden gems?</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/car-boat-rentals-cruises/index.html" source="/car-boat-rentals-cruises/index.html">
    <title>Rentals &amp;amp; Cruises -</title>
    <section name="Car Rentals in Rhodes">Choosing the cheapest option isn’t always the best choice! Here’s a list of reliable car rental companies in Rhodes: KION Rhodes Car Rentals Rent A Moto &amp;amp; Cars City Club J&amp;amp;D Rent a CarAirport Auto Tour Rent A Car Marathon Rent A Car Airport EPSILON rent a car Car rental Faliraki HB Efrem Rent A Car A ONE RENTALS – Faliraki Rent a Moto, Scooter, ATV &amp;amp; Car</section>
    <section name="Hit the Road! Scooter and Motorcycle Rentals in Rhodes">Rhodes is a wonderful place for experienced riders! If you’re not familiar with scooters or motorcycles, it might be best to consider other options. However, for those who have experience, riding a scooter in Rhodes can be truly magical!</section>
    <section name="Motorcycle Rentals">Here are some reliable companies for scooter, motorcycle, or ADV rentals: A ONE RENTALS – FALIRAKIMOTO ROLLCity Club Rent a Car &amp;amp; Motorbikes LindosMax Moto-Rent a motoRent A Moto Tony’sQueen Rental Car and Moto Rhodes A ONE RENTALS – FALIRAKIMOTO ROLLCity Club Rent a Car &amp;amp; Motorbikes LindosMax Moto-Rent a motoRent A Moto Tony’sQueen Rental Car and Moto Rhodes A ONE RENTALS – FALIRAKI MOTO ROLL City Club Rent a Car &amp;amp; Motorbikes Lindos Max Moto-Rent a moto Rent A Moto Tony’s Queen Rental Car and Moto Rhodes</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/index.html" source="/listings/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark C59M+R4 Ialysos Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark C5F6+29 Ialysos Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 7539+JX Kolympia Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 8WR8+F9 Kameiros Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 33RP+CG Lindos Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85RW+4Q Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes +1Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86M3+MM Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes +1Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 86M5+4C Faliraki Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/20/index.html" source="/listings/page/20/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 20 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">85QX+PQ Faliraki Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C5HX+CP Ialysos Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C59H+9X Ialysos Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C47M+WC Kremasti Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6G7+W5 Rhodes Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C584+QJ Ialysos Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C5C5+99 Ialysos Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C5C4+P7 Ialysos Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6VJ+66 Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/18/index.html" source="/listings/page/18/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 18 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">854H+P8 Kallithea Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6G4+7J Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C6PG+GM Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C6JM+C5 Rhodes Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark C6J8+8Q Rhodes Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark C6WG+W2 Rhodes Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark 643R+83 Archangelos Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 86P5+47 Faliraki Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 646R+HP Stegna Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark F63C+5J Rhodes Burger Time Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/9/index.html" source="/listings/page/9/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 9 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">C6WF+WQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 837W+Q3 Ψινθος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C575+W2 Ialysos Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 96P6+FQ Koskinou Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 9458+RP Maritsa Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 9469+PH Maritsa Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 86X3+J9 Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6VG+PQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark F628+GH Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark F638+2Q Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/11/index.html" source="/listings/page/11/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 11 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 7528+58 Kolympia Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+WQ Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 3293+WM Lardos Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark WVH5+MF Plimmiri Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 7528+2M Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 539W+2J Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 538V+MF Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 646R+RH Stegna Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/7/index.html" source="/listings/page/7/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 7 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">F629+GX Rhodes Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark C6HM+RG Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 3RXW+QX Profilia Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 8WQX+W7 Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 64JP+GF Αρχάγγελος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 745R+GP Archangelos Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 4PJQ+42 Monolithos Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 6VG3+WX Embonas Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7259+7Q Platania Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/6/index.html" source="/listings/page/6/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 6 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">C584+GQ Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C6XF+5R Rhodes Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C6WG+W3 Rhodes Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C6XC+9H Rhodes Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+8P Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 7536+JM Kolympia Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 75R7+65 Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+W7 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86V2+32 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark F62C+G6 Rhodes Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/17/index.html" source="/listings/page/17/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 17 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">C6V5+88 Ρόδος C6VG+P2 Rhodes 86W2+3G Faliraki C6XG+79 Rhodes 4Q2X+PF Νότια Ρόδος 86V2+R9 Faliraki C429+V9 Kremasti 86M5+73 Faliraki 86P2+GW Faliraki C6X9+JQ Rhodes Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/10/index.html" source="/listings/page/10/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 10 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">85XW+M9 Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C58F+VG Ialysos Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark C46F+V2 Kremasti Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark 6478+8C Archangelos Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark 75R7+54 Afantou Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark 85PF+7Q Kalithies Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark 85VX+4X Faliraki Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark 86P2+7W Faliraki Gyros Time Quick view Bookmark 85PX+97 Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark C6XC+68 Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/19/index.html" source="/listings/page/19/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 19 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">C6XG+6X Rhodes Brunch Spots Quick view Bookmark C6MQ+67 Rhodes Brunch Spots Quick view Bookmark F628+CG Rhodes Brunch Spots Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+F7 Faliraki Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark F63F+6W Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 85VX+5X Faliraki Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark C5C3+QW Ialysos Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 96CF+XX Ammoudes Greek Cuizine - Gourmet +1Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 86W2+7C Faliraki Greek Cuizine - Gourmet +1Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark C6X8+VV Rhodes Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/8/index.html" source="/listings/page/8/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 8 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">7X68+54 Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 836W+WW Καλλιθέα Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 837W+P5 Ψινθος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6MG+PJ Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C47G+JG Kremasti Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark 94PP+MM Pastida Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C6X9+Q9 Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C6XC+4C Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 6478+7H Archangelos Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/21/index.html" source="/listings/page/21/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 21 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">Ρόδου - Λίνδου Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 86P2+RH Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85RX+2Q Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark C6VG+58 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 7R75+JH Siana Top Places Quick view Bookmark 64PX+8R Archangelos Top Places Quick view Bookmark 7WGV+C8 Profitis Ilias Top Places Quick view Bookmark 8WPC+8H Kameiros Top Places Quick view Bookmark Ακτή Σαχτούρη Top Places Quick view Bookmark 7437+5C Archangelos Top Places Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/4/index.html" source="/listings/page/4/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 4 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">C6XG+87 Rhodes 85QX+9C Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 85QX+RQ Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 85QW+9X Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark VQRF+2R Νότια Ρόδος Top Places Quick view Bookmark C6HG+JP Rhodes 85MX+RH Faliraki Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86R2+X4 Faliraki Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/3/index.html" source="/listings/page/3/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 3 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">C5C4+5P Ialysos Sports Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+8Q Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Brunch Spots Quick view Bookmark 33RP+67 Lindos Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Greek Cuizine - Gourmet Quick view Bookmark 33F4+Q3 Pefki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Brunch Spots, Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark C589+Q2 Ialysos Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark F63F+4R Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark F63G+58 Rhodes F63G+58 Rhodes Nightlife In Rhodes Quick view Bookmark 7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/12/index.html" source="/listings/page/12/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 12 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">C6J7+W9 Rhodes Burger Time Quick view Bookmark C6C4+7W Sgourou Burger Time Quick view Bookmark C6WF+VM Rhodes Burger Time Quick view Bookmark C6XF+2C Rhodes Burger Time Quick view Bookmark 86G2+9R Καλλιθέα Brunch Spots Quick view Bookmark 86C5+HG Καλλιθέα Brunch Spots Quick view Bookmark F62C+G2 Rhodes Brunch Spots Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+CQ Faliraki Brunch Spots Quick view Bookmark 86R3+9C Faliraki Brunch Spots Quick view Bookmark 4Q2X+VM Νότια Ρόδος Top Places Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/2/index.html" source="/listings/page/2/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 2 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">86R3+CC Faliraki Burger Time Quick view Bookmark 86J5+RM Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes +1Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 7535+VC Kolympia Sports Bars Quick view Bookmark 7537+98 Kolympia Sports Bars Quick view Bookmark 85PW+6V Rhodes Sports Bars Quick view Bookmark 85PW+HH Faliraki Sports Bars Quick view Bookmark 85PW+HP Faliraki Sports Bars Quick view Bookmark C6QP+CC Rhodes Sports Bars Quick view Bookmark F62C+VM Rhodes Sports Bars Quick view Bookmark C59M+H7 Ialysos Sports Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/13/index.html" source="/listings/page/13/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 13 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">94XW+M2 Ialisos Top Places Quick view Bookmark Isiodou Top Places Quick view Bookmark 923W+5R Top Places Quick view Bookmark 86F4+MX Καλλιθέα Top Places Quick view Bookmark C6GC+Q4 Rhodes Top Places Quick view Bookmark C6V5+98 Ρόδος Top Places Quick view Bookmark 3QM9+RJ Nótia Ródos Top Places Quick view Bookmark C6VH+V2 Rhodes Top Places Quick view Bookmark 33RJ+2X Λίνδος Top Places Quick view Bookmark F62G+FJ Rhodes Top Places Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/5/index.html" source="/listings/page/5/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 5 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C47G+PQ Kremasti Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 85PW+9X Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 85XW+Q9 Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 85PX+W6 Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C6HM+V2 Rhodes Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 96XG+3W Rhodes Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C66G+PG Rhodes Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C584+H9 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listings/page/14/index.html" source="/listings/page/14/index.html">
    <title>Listings Archive - Page 14 of 22 -</title>
    <section name="Archives:Listings">83Q5+VV Rhodes Top Places Quick view Bookmark 72FF+6P Eleousa Top Places Quick view Bookmark 4PFG+RC Monolithos Top Places Quick view Bookmark 96HP+3W Rhodes Top Places Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/getting-around-rhodes-taxi-and-bus-options/index.html" source="/getting-around-rhodes-taxi-and-bus-options/index.html">
    <title>Getting Around Rhodes: Taxi and Bus Options -</title>
    <section name="Getting Around Rhodes: Taxi and Bus Options">Local Tips Mar 22 Share post Rhodes offers convenient transportation options, whether you prefer traveling by bus or taxi. Understanding the available services will help you navigate the island efficiently.</section>
    <section name="Bus Services in Rhodes">Public buses are a cost-effective way to explore Rhodes, with different companies serving the eastern and western parts of the island. Areas Served:Airport, Ixia, Ialysos, Trianda, Kritika, Kanari Coast Ticket Prices:Vary depending on the distance More Information:https://rodospublictransport.gr Areas Served:Kallithea, Faliraki, Kolymbia, Haraki, Lindos, Pefki, Prasonisi Ticket Prices:Vary based on the route More Information:www.ktelrodou.gr Both bus services provide detailed route maps, schedules, and ticket purchasing options on their websites.</section>
    <section name="Taxi Services in Rhodes">Taxis are a convenient and faster alternative to public transport, especially for direct transfers or late-night travel. Each area in Rhodes has its own taxi station with a dedicated contact number. More Information:https://www.rhodes-taxi.gr</section>
    <section name="Choosing the Best Transport Option">For budget-friendly travel:Buses are the best option. For faster, direct routes:Taxis offer convenience, especially for short distances. For exploring multiple locations in one day:Consider a taxi service or a combination of bus routes. No matter which option you choose, Rhodes’ transportation network makes it easy to experience the island’s stunning landscapes, historical sites, and beautiful beaches. local-busestaxitransporation taxitransporation transporation</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/rhodes-insider-guide-13-local-tips-for-an-authentic-hassle-free-holiday/index.html" source="/rhodes-insider-guide-13-local-tips-for-an-authentic-hassle-free-holiday/index.html">
    <title>Rhodes Insider Guide: 13 Local Tips for an Authentic &amp;amp; Hassle-Free Holiday -</title>
    <section name="Rhodes Insider Guide: 13 Local Tips for an Authentic &amp;amp; Hassle-Free Holiday">Local Tips Mar 05 Share post When visiting Rhodes, Greece, it’s essential to embrace the local culture and practices to enhance your travel experience. Here are some valuable tips to help you navigate the island like a local, ensuring you save money and enjoy your stay to the fullest. Tips for a Great Experience in Rhodes: Use Cash: Locals prefer cash and often offer discounts for cash payments. This can lead to savings on your purchases. Use Local ATMs: Withdraw cash (Euros) from Greek bank ATMs (e.g., Piraeus, Alpha Bank, Eurobank, Ethniki) to avoid high fees from multinational machines. Always check the fees and exchange rates before withdrawing. Ask for Prices: Request a menu or price list wherever you go before you order or buy something. This helps avoid surprises and ensures you know what to expect. Rent a Car: Rhodes is a large island, and if you want to explore its beauty, renting a car is the best option. It will save you both money and time, allowing you to discover hidden gems. Drive Safely: Always keep a safe distance from other vehicles, especially taxis, buses, and quads. Road safety is crucial for a pleasant driving experience. Beach Access: Almost all beaches have an area without umbrellas and sunbeds, where you can lie down with your towel (and your own umbrella if you have one) for free. Use the ‘MyCoast’ app to find spots where you can enjoy the beach without paying for a sunbed. Windy West Side: The west side of the island is almost always windy, making it ideal for windsurfing. If you’re interested in this sport, explore Google Maps to find over 15 great spots. Stay Hydrated: From June to August, temperatures soar, and crowds gather. Always carry water and fruit. You can also find cold drinks, snacks, and refreshments at the numerous kiosks along the streets. Sun Protection: Don’t forget to apply sunscreen to avoid burns, especially during peak sun hours. Avoid Tap Water: Drink bottled water unless you have a proper filtration system or have been assured that the tap water in your accommodation is safe to drink. Experience Local Festivals “Panigiri”: Enjoy local festivals known as “panigiria” in the villages, especially in July and August. These events offer great food, drinks, and authentic souvlaki. Dine in Villages: Visit village tavernas for homemade local dishes and an authentic Greek experience. This is a great way to taste traditional cuisine and support local businesses. Trust your Hotel:Almost all small and medium-sized hotels offer a variety of services through trusted partners, such as excursions, car rentals, cruises, and taxi services . Each hotel owner has carefully selected the best options to ensure an excellent experience for their guests. By following these tips, you’ll be well-equipped to enjoy all that Rhodes has to offer while immersing yourself in the local culture.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/free-parking-in-rhodes-town-your-guide-to-akantia-parking-mini-bus-shuttle-service/index.html" source="/free-parking-in-rhodes-town-your-guide-to-akantia-parking-mini-bus-shuttle-service/index.html">
    <title>Free Parking in Rhodes Town: Your Guide to Akantia Parking &amp;amp; Mini Bus Shuttle Service -</title>
    <section name="Free Parking in Rhodes Town: Akantia Parking &amp;amp; Mini Bus Shuttle Service">Finding a convenient place to park in Rhodes Town can be difficult, especially during the busy tourist season. TheAkania municipal parking lotoffers the perfect solution for visitors who want to explore the Medieval City and Rhodes city center without the stress of searching for parking.</section>
    <section name="Why Choose Akantia Free Parking in Rhodes?">Completely Free:No parking fees or time limits. Prime Location:Located next to the old commercial port, easy to find and access. 24/7 Access:The parking lot is open day and night, so you can park any time—even at 2:00 AM! Safe &amp;amp; Spacious:Well-lit and secure, with plenty of parking spaces.</section>
    <section name="Free Mini Bus Shuttle to Rhodes City Center">One of the best features of Akantia Parking is thefree mini bus shuttlethat connects the parking lot to the heart of Rhodes Town: Operating Hours:Every 20 minutes from 07:00 to 22:00 during the tourist season. Quick Ride:The mini bus shuttle takes about 10-15 minutes to reach the city center. Drop-Off Point:Stops right by the Town Hall and the main gates of the Medieval City—just 1.5 km from the parking lot. Family Friendly:Ideal for families, groups, and solo travelers.</section>
    <section name="How to Use Akantia Parking &amp;amp; Mini Bus Shuttle">Drive to Akantia Parking(see location onGoogle Maps). Park your car for free—no tickets or reservations needed. Board the free mini bus shuttleat the designated stop in the parking lot. Enjoy your dayin Rhodes Town, knowing your car is safe and parking is hassle-free.</section>
    <section name="Insider Tip">Even if you plan to enjoy Rhodes Town late at night, Akantia parking remains open, so you can return to your car at any hour. The mini bus shuttle runs until 22:00, so plan your return accordingly or enjoy a pleasant walk back (about 15-20 minutes). For more information, visit theofficial Rhodes Municipality websiteor ask at local tourist information centers. If you’re visiting Rhodes Town and want a stress-free experience,Akantia Parkingwith its free mini bus shuttle is your best choice for convenient and secure parking. Make the most of your time exploring the beautiful Medieval City and vibrant city center of Rhodes! free mini bus Rhodesfree parking Rhodesparking near Medieval City RhodesRhodes Old Town parkingRhodes town parking free parking Rhodesparking near Medieval City RhodesRhodes Old Town parkingRhodes town parking parking near Medieval City RhodesRhodes Old Town parkingRhodes town parking Rhodes Old Town parkingRhodes town parking Rhodes town parking</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/rhodes-airport-taxi-prices/index.html" source="/rhodes-airport-taxi-prices/index.html">
    <title>Rhodes Airport Taxi Prices 2025: Official Fixed Fares &amp;amp; Transfers to Rhodes Town, Faliraki, Lindos, Ixia &amp;amp; Ialyssos -</title>
    <section name="Why Choose a Taxi from Rhodes Airport?">Choosing ataxi from Rhodes Airportis the fastest and most convenient way to reach your hotel or accommodation anywhere on the island. Official airport taxis are available 24/7 at the taxi rank just outside the arrivals terminal. Fixed fares mean you know exactly what you will pay, with no surprises.</section>
    <section name="Benefits of Taking a Taxi from Rhodes Airport:">Official, fixed pricesfor popular destinations No hidden fees– prices include luggage and up to 4 passengers Direct transferto your hotel, villa, or apartment No waiting for buses or searching for shuttle services Available day and night</section>
    <section name="Rhodes Airport Transfers for Groups and Families">If you are traveling with a larger group or require a minivan, you can pre-book aRhodes airport transferonline. Minivan and luxury vehicle options are available, with prices slightly higher than standard taxis. Online booking ensures your driver will be waiting for you on arrival, even during peak season.</section>
    <section name="How do I find a taxi at Rhodes Airport?">Taxis are available 24/7 at the official taxi rank just outside the arrivals area. For peace of mind, you can also pre-book your taxi or private transfer onlinehere!</section>
    <section name="Can I pay by credit card?">Most taxis accept cash (euros), and some accept credit cards. It’s always a good idea to confirm payment options with your driver before starting your journey. If you are traveling from Rhodes Airport with 4 people and 4 suitcases (one per person), here’s what you need to know about luggage charges and taxi size: Standard Taxi Capacity:A regular taxi in Rhodes can usually accommodate up to 4 passengers and a typical luggage allowance such as:3 medium suitcases + 2 cabin bags2 large suitcases + 1 medium6 cabin suitcases1 extra-large suitcase + 2 cabin bagsIf each passenger has a large suitcase, it may exceed the standard taxi’s luggage capacity, especially if the suitcases are bulky or if you have additional hand luggage. 3 medium suitcases + 2 cabin bags2 large suitcases + 1 medium6 cabin suitcases1 extra-large suitcase + 2 cabin bags Excess Luggage Charge:If your luggage exceeds the standard allowance for a regular taxi, you will need to select the “Excessive Luggage” service. In this case, you will be provided with a station wagon taxi or a minivan. The extra charge for excessive luggage is€10 one way(or €20 for a round trip). Minivan Option:For groups of 4 with large suitcases, a minivan is often the best solution. A minivan can accommodate up to 8 passengers and 8 medium/large suitcases (plus cabin bags), ensuring comfort and no issues with luggage space. Extra Charges per Bag:According to the official taxi price list, there is also a small surcharge for each baggage item over 10 kg, which is€0.43 per bagHowever, for most pre-booked transfers and reputable taxi services, the main concern is the total luggage volume rather than the number of bags. Summary Table: Tip:If you are 4 people with 4 large suitcases, it is recommended to book a minivan or request the “Excessive Luggage” service during your booking to avoid any issues at the airport and ensure a comfortable transfer Special Items:For bulky items (baby strollers, wheelchairs, surfboards, golf clubs, etc.), always select the “Excessive Luggage” option when booking Conclusion:A standard taxi is usually sufficient for 4 people with small/medium luggage. For 4 people with 4 large suitcases or additional bulky items, a minivan is recommended, with an extra charge of €10 for excessive luggage. There is also a minor surcharge of €0.43 per bag over 10 kg, but this is less commonly applied in pre-booked transfers</section>
    <section name="Popular Areas to Stay in Rhodes">Rhodes offers a variety of destinations for every traveler: Rhodes Town:History, shopping, nightlife Ixia &amp;amp; Ialyssos:Beach resorts close to the city Faliraki:Lively beach, water sports, nightlife Lindos:Picturesque village, historic acropolis Pefkos &amp;amp; Gennadi – Kiotari:Relaxed, family-friendly resorts</section>
    <section name="Summary of Rhodes Airport Taxi Prices (2025)">Rhodes Airport to Rhodes Town:€27–29 Rhodes Airport to Ixia:€21 Rhodes Airport to Ialyssos:€18 Rhodes Airport to Faliraki:€31 Rhodes Airport to Lindos:€74 Rhodes Airport to Gennadi – Kiotari:€90 These are the official, fixed taxi fares for up to 4 passengers, ensuring a hassle-free start to your holiday in Rhodes. For larger groups, families, or special requests, consider booking a private transfer in advance for the best experience. Book your Rhodes airport taxi or transfer today and enjoy a smooth arrival on the beautiful island of Rhodes! rhodestaxitaxipricetransporation taxitaxipricetransporation taxipricetransporation transporation</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/a-month-by-month-guide-to-rhodes-weather-what-to-expect/index.html" source="/a-month-by-month-guide-to-rhodes-weather-what-to-expect/index.html">
    <title>A Month-by-Month Guide to Rhodes' Weather: What to Expect -</title>
    <section name="A Month-by-Month Guide to Rhodes’ Weather: What to Expect">Local Tips Mar 21 Share post Rhodes, the sun-kissed gem of the Aegean, enjoys a Mediterranean climate with mild winters and hot, sun-drenched summers. However, temperatures can vary depending on the season, and factors like wind and humidity can influence how the weather actually feels. Here’s a month-by-month breakdown to help you prepare for your visit:</section>
    <section name="January – The Coolest Month">Average Temperature:12-15°C Feels Like:9-11°C with humidity and wind, though milder days can feel closer to 14-16°C. What to Expect:Cool temperatures, occasional rain, and strong breezes. A jacket is necessary, especially at night.</section>
    <section name="February – Slowly Warming Up">Average Temperature:13-16°C Feels Like:12-14°C on cloudy or windy days. What to Expect:Slightly warmer than January, with cool evenings and occasional rain showers.</section>
    <section name="March – The First Hints of Spring">Average Temperature:14-17°C Feels Like:12-14°C when windy, but sunny days can feel like 16-18°C. What to Expect:Days are getting longer, and the first signs of spring appear, though it’s still too cool for beach weather.</section>
    <section name="April – Spring in Full Bloom">Average Temperature:17-19°C Feels Like:18-20°C on sunny afternoons, but evenings can be chilly (12-14°C). What to Expect:Warm, pleasant days and cooler nights. A light jacket is still needed after sunset.</section>
    <section name="May – The Start of Beach Season">Average Temperature:20-23°C Feels Like:22-25°C during the day, with evenings around 18-20°C. What to Expect:The sea is still cool, but days are warm and ideal for outdoor activities.</section>
    <section name="June – Summer Arrives">Average Temperature:25-28°C Feels Like:27-30°C in the sun, with the shade offering a comfortable 25-27°C. What to Expect:Long, sunny days with little rainfall. The sea is perfect for swimming.</section>
    <section name="August – The Hottest Month">Average Temperature:28-31°C Feels Like:34-36°C, though sea breezes can provide some relief. What to Expect:Intense heat, perfect for beach days and water activities.</section>
    <section name="September – Summer Lingers">Average Temperature:25-28°C Feels Like:28-30°C, with cooler, pleasant evenings. What to Expect:A great time to visit as crowds thin out, but the weather remains warm.</section>
    <section name="October – A Perfect Balance">Average Temperature:21-24°C Feels Like:22-24°C during the day, with nights cooling to 17-19°C. What to Expect:Ideal for sightseeing and outdoor adventures, with mild weather and fewer tourists.</section>
    <section name="December – Mild Winter Begins">Average Temperature:13-16°C Feels Like:11-13°C, especially on rainy or windy days. What to Expect:A cool but comfortable winter, with a chance of rain and crisp evenings.</section>
    <section name="Rhodes: A Year-Round Destination">Rhodes’ Mediterranean climate ensures there’s never a bad time to visit. Whether you prefer the summer’s sun-soaked beaches or the cooler, quieter charm of winter, this island offers something for every traveler. Plan accordingly, and enjoy everything Rhodes has to offer, no matter the season! informationlocal factsweather local factsweather weather</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/discover-rhodes-like-a-local-the-ultimate-insider-guide-for-your-dream-holidays/index.html" source="/discover-rhodes-like-a-local-the-ultimate-insider-guide-for-your-dream-holidays/index.html">
    <title>Rhodes Greece . Local Guide-Advisor! -</title>
    <section name="Discover Rhodes Like a Local: The Ultimate Insider Guide for Your Dream Holidays">Are you planning your holidays in Rhodes and want to make the most of your trip? Rhodes is one of the top travel destinations in Greece, famous for its stunning beaches, rich history, and vibrant culture. But to truly experience the best of Rhodes, you need more than just the usual tourist information—you need local insight!</section>
    <section name="Why Trust a Local’s Guide to Rhodes?">As a lifelong resident of Rhodes, I know every corner of this beautiful island. I’ve created a comprehensive, independent local guide that gathers all the must-see attractions, hidden gems, authentic food spots, and practical tips in one place. For a very small cost, you get access to unique knowledge that will save you both time and money.</section>
    <section name="What Makes This Rhodes Guide Different?">Unbiased Local Tips:Discover secret beaches, traditional villages, and authentic experiences only locals know. Top Rhodes Attractions:Explore the UNESCO Medieval Old Town, the Acropolis of Lindos, Valley of the Butterflies, Prasonisi, and more. Best Beaches in Rhodes:Find out where locals swim—Faliraki, Anthony Quinn Bay, Tsambika, and secluded coves. Where to Eat in Rhodes:Taste real Greek cuisine at the best tavernas, local cafes, and food markets. Accommodation Advice:Get recommendations for every budget—hotels, apartments, and unique stays. Activities &amp;amp; Experiences:Hiking, water sports, cultural events, and seasonal tips for every traveler. Money &amp;amp; Time Saving Hacks:Avoid tourist traps, discover free attractions, and get practical travel advice.</section>
    <section name="Save Time and Money—Everything You Need in One Place">Searching for reliable information online can be overwhelming and time-consuming. Most travel sites are filled with sponsored content and generic advice. With this local guide, you get: All the best information in one place—no more endless web searches. Completely independent and unsponsored recommendations—genuine, tried-and-tested tips. Insider secretsthat help you make the most of your time and budget in Rhodes.</section>
    <section name="Why Rhodes Is the Place to Be in 2025">Rhodes is trending as one of the most sought-after Greek islands, with a surge in bookings and online searches for “Rhodes attractions,” “best beaches in Rhodes,” “things to do in Rhodes,” and “where to eat in Rhodes.” This guide covers everything you need to know to experience the island like a true insider. Unlock the real Rhodes for a very small cost. Buy my local guide and discover the island through the eyes of someone who calls it home—saving you both time and money with trusted, non-sponsored advice! Disclaimer:This is an informational travel guide created by a local resident. It does not offer licensed tour guide services or personal guided tours. All recommendations are based on personal experience and local knowledge. Ready to explore Rhodes like a local? Get your insider guide today and make your holidays truly unforgettable! Rhodes, Rhodes travel guide, Rhodes local guide, things to do in Rhodes, Rhodes attractions, best beaches in Rhodes, where to eat in Rhodes, Rhodes tips, Rhodes insider guide, Rhodes accommodation, Rhodes activities, summer in Rhodes, family holidays Rhodes, authentic Rhodes, hidden gems Rhodes. explorerhodeslocalinforhodesRhodeslikealocalThingsToDoInRhodes localinforhodesRhodeslikealocalThingsToDoInRhodes rhodesRhodeslikealocalThingsToDoInRhodes RhodeslikealocalThingsToDoInRhodes ThingsToDoInRhodes</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/locals-insider-guide-12-tips-for-an-authentic-and-hassle-free-holiday-in-rhodes/index.html" source="/locals-insider-guide-12-tips-for-an-authentic-and-hassle-free-holiday-in-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Rhodes Insider Guide: 13 Local Tips for an Authentic &amp;amp; Hassle-Free Holiday -</title>
    <section name="Rhodes Insider Guide: 13 Local Tips for an Authentic &amp;amp; Hassle-Free Holiday">Local Tips Mar 05 Share post When visiting Rhodes, Greece, it’s essential to embrace the local culture and practices to enhance your travel experience. Here are some valuable tips to help you navigate the island like a local, ensuring you save money and enjoy your stay to the fullest. Tips for a Great Experience in Rhodes: Use Cash: Locals prefer cash and often offer discounts for cash payments. This can lead to savings on your purchases. Use Local ATMs: Withdraw cash (Euros) from Greek bank ATMs (e.g., Piraeus, Alpha Bank, Eurobank, Ethniki) to avoid high fees from multinational machines. Always check the fees and exchange rates before withdrawing. Ask for Prices: Request a menu or price list wherever you go before you order or buy something. This helps avoid surprises and ensures you know what to expect. Rent a Car: Rhodes is a large island, and if you want to explore its beauty, renting a car is the best option. It will save you both money and time, allowing you to discover hidden gems. Drive Safely: Always keep a safe distance from other vehicles, especially taxis, buses, and quads. Road safety is crucial for a pleasant driving experience. Beach Access: Almost all beaches have an area without umbrellas and sunbeds, where you can lie down with your towel (and your own umbrella if you have one) for free. Use the ‘MyCoast’ app to find spots where you can enjoy the beach without paying for a sunbed. Windy West Side: The west side of the island is almost always windy, making it ideal for windsurfing. If you’re interested in this sport, explore Google Maps to find over 15 great spots. Stay Hydrated: From June to August, temperatures soar, and crowds gather. Always carry water and fruit. You can also find cold drinks, snacks, and refreshments at the numerous kiosks along the streets. Sun Protection: Don’t forget to apply sunscreen to avoid burns, especially during peak sun hours. Avoid Tap Water: Drink bottled water unless you have a proper filtration system or have been assured that the tap water in your accommodation is safe to drink. Experience Local Festivals “Panigiri”: Enjoy local festivals known as “panigiria” in the villages, especially in July and August. These events offer great food, drinks, and authentic souvlaki. Dine in Villages: Visit village tavernas for homemade local dishes and an authentic Greek experience. This is a great way to taste traditional cuisine and support local businesses. Trust your Hotel:Almost all small and medium-sized hotels offer a variety of services through trusted partners, such as excursions, car rentals, cruises, and taxi services . Each hotel owner has carefully selected the best options to ensure an excellent experience for their guests. By following these tips, you’ll be well-equipped to enjoy all that Rhodes has to offer while immersing yourself in the local culture.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/post-category/local-tips/index.html" source="/post-category/local-tips/index.html">
    <title>Local Tips Archives -</title>
    <section name="Category:Local Tips">Discover Rhodes Like a Local: The Ultimate Insider Guide for Your Dream Holidays Are you planning your holidays in Rhodes and want to make the most of your trip? Rhodes is one of the top travel destinations in Greece, famous for its stunning beaches, rich history, and vibrant culture. But to truly experience the best […] About +1Local Tips Rhodes Airport Taxi Prices 2025 – Fixed Fares to Popular Destinations Official Fixed Taxi Fares from Rhodes Airport Destination Fixed Taxi Fare Distance Estimated Time Rhodes Town €27–29 14 km 20–30 min Ixia €21 10 km 15–20 min Ialyssos €18 7–12 km 10–20 min Faliraki €31 18–20 km 20–30 min Lindos €74 50 km 50–60 […] Local Tips Free Parking in Rhodes Town: Akantia Parking &amp;amp; Mini Bus Shuttle Service Finding a convenient place to park in Rhodes Town can be difficult, especially during the busy tourist season. The Akania municipal parking lot offers the perfect solution for visitors who want to explore the Medieval City and Rhodes city center without the stress of searching […] Local Tips Rhodes offers convenient transportation options, whether you prefer traveling by bus or taxi. Understanding the available services will help you navigate the island efficiently. Bus Services in Rhodes Public buses are a cost-effective way to explore Rhodes, with different companies serving the eastern and western parts of the island. 🚌 Western Rhodes – D.E.S. RODA […] Local Tips Rhodes, the sun-kissed gem of the Aegean, enjoys a Mediterranean climate with mild winters and hot, sun-drenched summers. However, temperatures can vary depending on the season, and factors like wind and humidity can influence how the weather actually feels. Here’s a month-by-month breakdown to help you prepare for your visit: January – The Coolest Month […] Local Tips When visiting Rhodes, Greece, it’s essential to embrace the local culture and practices to enhance your travel experience. Here are some valuable tips to help you navigate the island like a local, ensuring you save money and enjoy your stay to the fullest. Tips for a Great Experience in Rhodes: By following these tips, you’ll […] Local Tips</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/afantou-beach/index.html" source="/listing/afantou-beach/index.html">
    <title>Afantou Beach -</title>
    <section name="Afantou BeachVerified listing">Stretching over 5 kilometers, Afantou Beach offers vast space with crystal-clear, deep, refreshing waters. It's particularly popular among families with young children, thanks to its ample room. While some sections of the beach are well-organized, others are more rustic, but a few spots truly stand out. 📍Afandou Beach 📌  Local's recommendations: 📍Vammos Beach Bar Known for its lively atmosphere, Vammos Beach Bar hosts wild parties with great music, especially on Sundays when the vibe is exceptional. 📍Sundalia on the Beach For more relaxed moments, Sundalia offers a beautiful setting with excellent drinks and food, perfect for unwinding after a swim. 75MG+75 Αφάντου, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 75MG+75 Αφάντου, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/prophet-elias-monastery-faliraki/index.html" source="/listing/prophet-elias-monastery-faliraki/index.html">
    <title>Prophet Elias Monastery - Faliraki -</title>
    <section name="Prophet Elias Monastery - FalirakiVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Situated at an elevation of over 500 meters, thismonasteryoffers a breathtaking view of Faliraki, Antony Quinn Bay, and Ladiko Beach. As the sun sets, the lights from the road and hotels combined with the moonlight create a unique atmosphere! 📍Prophet Elias Monastery 📍Prophet Amos Monastery 🔑Tips: All times are suitable for a visit, but be cautious on the steep road leading up. It’s best to have an experienced driver. If you’re into hiking, there’s a trail from theProphet AmosMonasterythat takes you to Prophet Elias in 15-20 minutes through a cool, shaded forest path. 86F4+MX Καλλιθέα, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 86F4+MX Καλλιθέα, Ελλάδα Faliraki Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/taverna-fountoukli/index.html" source="/listing/taverna-fountoukli/index.html">
    <title>Taverna Fountoukli -</title>
    <section name="Taverna FountoukliVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Taverna Fountoukli 🌐Taverna Fountoukli 7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος, Ελλάδα Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 836W+WW Καλλιθέα Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/victoria-beach-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/victoria-beach-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Victoria - Beach Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Victoria - Beach RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Victoria - Beach Restaurant 🌐Victoria - Beach Restaurant 86J5+RM Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86J5+RM Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7539+JX Kolympia Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark WVH5+MF Plimmiri Fish Taverna Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/bee-museum-a-unique-experience-in-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/bee-museum-a-unique-experience-in-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Bee Museum: A Unique Experience in Rhodes! -</title>
    <section name="Bee Museum: A Unique Experience in Rhodes!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Visit the only bee museum in Greece! Experts say that if bees were to disappear, humans might follow. The museum offers a fascinating look at the hierarchy and functioning of these incredible creatures. At the Bee Museum in Rhodes, you can learn why ancient Egyptians, Indians, and Greeks considered honey and bees not only as therapeutic but also beneficial for longevity. 🔑Don’t forget to pass by the museum shop to sample some of the products and delicious treats made with local honey! And by the way, in local markets around Rhodes, you can find some of the most delicious honey! 📍Bee Museum of Rhodes 94FW+94 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 94FW+94 Rhodes, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/gregorys/index.html" source="/listing/gregorys/index.html">
    <title>Gregory's -</title>
    <section name="Gregory'sVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Gregory's 🌐Gregory's C6XF+5R Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XF+5R Rhodes, Greece Sandwich Bakery Coffee Rhodes Town Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/mikes-bar/index.html" source="/listing/mikes-bar/index.html">
    <title>Mikes Bar -</title>
    <section name="Mikes BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Mikes Bar 🌐Mikes Bar 85PW+HP Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85PW+HP Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Sports Bars No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/2645/index.html" source="/listing/2645/index.html">
    <title>To Limeri tou Listi -</title>
    <section name="To Limeri tou ListiVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍To Limeri tou Listi 🌐To Limeri tou Listi 3RXW+QX Profilia, GreeceGet Directions 3RXW+QX Profilia, Greece South Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/health-fitness-hubs/index.html" source="/listing/health-fitness-hubs/index.html">
    <title>Health &amp;amp; Fitness Hubs -</title>
    <section name="Health &amp;amp; Fitness HubsVerified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next "It is a shame for a person to grow old without ever experiencing the beauty and strength that their body is capable of achieving."— Socrates If you want to stay active during your holidays or don’t want to miss a workout, here are some great fitness centers to check out: 📍The Project_Cf Box Of Rhodes IG :The Project_Cf Box Of Rhodes 📍G.K Fitness Club by George Kazellis 🌐G.K Fitness Club by George Kazellis IG :G.K Fitness Club by George Kazellis 📍BlackBox Factory Rhodes 🌐BlackBox Factory Rhodes IG :BlackBox Factory Rhodes 📍ΕNathlon 🌐ΕNathlon IG :ΕNathlon 📍Bend Reality 🌐Bend Reality IG :Bend Reality C6HG+JP Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6HG+JP Rhodes, Greece Gym CrossFit CrossTraining Calisthenics Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/drosoulites-rakadiko/index.html" source="/listing/drosoulites-rakadiko/index.html">
    <title>Drosoulites - Rakadiko -</title>
    <section name="Drosoulites - RakadikoVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Drosoulites - Rakadiko 🌐Drosoulites - Rakadiko C6XC+4C Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XC+4C Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/tsaperdona-pizza-pasta/index.html" source="/listing/tsaperdona-pizza-pasta/index.html">
    <title>Tsaperdona Pizza Pasta -</title>
    <section name="Tsaperdona Pizza PastaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Tsaperdona pizza pasta 🌐Tsaperdona pizza pasta C5C5+99 Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C5C5+99 Ialysos, Greece Pasta Pizza Ialysos Ixia Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/alabama-sports-bar-and-grill/index.html" source="/listing/alabama-sports-bar-and-grill/index.html">
    <title>Alabama Sports Bar and Grill -</title>
    <section name="Alabama Sports Bar and GrillVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Alabama Sports Bar and Grill 🌐Alabama Sports Bar and Grill 85PW+6V Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 85PW+6V Rhodes, Greece Faliraki Sports Bars No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/dali-extraordinary-art-bistro/index.html" source="/listing/dali-extraordinary-art-bistro/index.html">
    <title>Dali Extraordinary Art Bistro -</title>
    <section name="Dali Extraordinary Art BistroVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Dali Extraordinary Art Bistro 🌐Dali Extraordinary Art Bistro F628+CG Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F628+CG Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Brunch Spots No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/red-sand-beach-a-hidden-gem-with-unique-beauty/index.html" source="/listing/red-sand-beach-a-hidden-gem-with-unique-beauty/index.html">
    <title>Red Sand Beach: A Hidden Gem with Unique Beauty -</title>
    <section name="Red Sand Beach: A Hidden Gem with Unique BeautyVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Red Sand Beach is a stunning location with its distinct red sand and crystal-clear waters. The setting is truly magical. However, accessing the beach by land can be challenging and even dangerous, requiring excellent physical condition. The easiest way to visit this red sand beach is by boat or on a day cruise. It's a must-see for those looking for something truly unique on the island! 📍Discover the charm ofRed Sand Beach 54M8+MH Αρχάγγελος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 54M8+MH Αρχάγγελος, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/la-esquina/index.html" source="/listing/la-esquina/index.html">
    <title>La Esquina -</title>
    <section name="La EsquinaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍La Esquina 🌐La Esquina 85VX+5X Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85VX+5X Faliraki, Greece Steak Faliraki Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/el-toro-steak-house/index.html" source="/listing/el-toro-steak-house/index.html">
    <title>El Toro Steak House -</title>
    <section name="El Toro Steak HouseVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍El Toro Steak House 🌐El Toro Steak House C6JP+XR Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6JP+XR Rhodes, Greece Steak Rhodes Town Greek Cuisine - Restaurant No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark Ρόδου - Λίνδου Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/tsambikos-restaurant-1977/index.html" source="/listing/tsambikos-restaurant-1977/index.html">
    <title>Tsambikos Restaurant 1977 -</title>
    <section name="Tsambikos Restaurant 1977Verified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Tsambikos Restaurant 1977 🌐Tsambikos Restaurant 1977 86M5+4C Faliraki, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 86M5+4C Faliraki, Ελλάδα Faliraki Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/stegna-kozas/index.html" source="/listing/stegna-kozas/index.html">
    <title>Stegna Kozas -</title>
    <section name="Stegna KozasVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Stegna Kozas 🌐Stegna Kozas 646R+HP Stegna, GreeceGet Directions 646R+HP Stegna, Greece Stegna - Archangelos Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/daily-cruises-2/index.html" source="/listing/daily-cruises-2/index.html">
    <title>Daily cruises -</title>
    <section name="Daily cruisesVerified listing">Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next For a very reasonable cost, you can embark on a fantastic cruise, visit famous beaches, and swim in stunning sea caves without wasting time in traffic! There are many options available, from lively party boats to more relaxed cruises. Some cruises even include drinks and meals! If you're traveling with a larger group, consider renting a private boat with a skipper for a more exclusive experience. Rhodes offers countless cruise options, and a quick online search will reveal plenty of choices to suit every taste! On daily cruises, you gonna find , what  suits you best!! 🌐Cruises Take a look here as well-I truly believe it’s worth your attention 🌐Rhodes Sea Lines C6XG+79 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XG+79 Rhodes, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/talonia/index.html" source="/listing/talonia/index.html">
    <title>T’alonia -</title>
    <section name="T’aloniaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍T’alonia 🌐T’alonia 85PF+7Q Kalithies, GreeceGet Directions 85PF+7Q Kalithies, Greece Faliraki Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/desert-rose/index.html" source="/listing/desert-rose/index.html">
    <title>Desert Rose Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Desert Rose RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Desert Rose Restaurant 🌐Desert Rose Restaurant 85RX+2Q Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85RX+2Q Faliraki, Greece Steak Rooftop Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/jet-ski-water-sports-ride-the-waves-of-fun/index.html" source="/listing/jet-ski-water-sports-ride-the-waves-of-fun/index.html">
    <title>Jet Ski &amp;amp; Water Sports: Ride the Waves of Fun! -</title>
    <section name="Jet Ski &amp;amp; Water Sports: Ride the Waves of Fun!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next If you’ve never tried jet skiing, now’s is the time! On the west side of the island, the sea is usually (99% of the times) calm, which means more speed and adrenaline for all your water sports adventures!! You can choose among jet ski, sofa, ringo, and much more! Try them all! You’re in for a blast and lots of laughs! 📌recommendation: While most water sports are similar, for jet skiing, the standout choice is 📍Faliraki Watersports (Kostas) 🌐Faliraki Watersports(Kostas) 9625+WH Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 9625+WH Faliraki, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/niceday-2/index.html" source="/listing/niceday-2/index.html">
    <title>NiceDay -</title>
    <section name="NiceDayVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍NiceDay 🌐NiceDay C6XC+9H Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XC+9H Rhodes, Greece Take Away Breakfast Sandwich Bakery Coffee Rhodes Town Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/fishing-trip-a-unique-experience-in-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/fishing-trip-a-unique-experience-in-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Fishing Trip: A Unique Experience in Rhodes! -</title>
    <section name="Fishing Trip: A Unique Experience in Rhodes!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next How would you like a mini-cruise lasting 3-5 hours where you not only learn how to fish but also enjoy a meal with the fish you catch? Sounds amazing, right? And it’s absolutely true! One of the best value-for-money activities in Rhodes, this experience is worth every penny. Definitely a must-do! 📌 Mr Local's recommendation: 📍Sostis Boat. The crew was friendly and very welcoming! 86P5+63 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86P5+63 Faliraki, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/monte-smith/index.html" source="/listing/monte-smith/index.html">
    <title>Monte Smith -</title>
    <section name="Monte SmithVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next If love at first sight had a home, this would be it! A famous spot for both locals and tourists, and in the evening, it's nothing short of romantic. 🔑Tips: Best times to visit:For a morning walk or jog (8:00 AM - 10:00 AM ). Αfternoon walks (after 18:00) or jogging at sunset offer the perfect combination of sunset and views! During the summer months (June-August), it gets very hot in the middle of the day. From 11:00 to 17:00, there’s often traffic from tourist buses showing off the site. Along the way, there are several spots where you can sit and capture incredible photos! 📍Monte Smith 📌Views: 📍View of the city 📍View of Ixia and Ialyssos 📍Portrait from trees 📍Best view for cars 📍Secret place to sit Isiodou, Rhodes 851 00, GreeceGet Directions Isiodou, Rhodes 851 00, Greece Rhodes Town Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/sarikas-bakery-patisserie/index.html" source="/listing/sarikas-bakery-patisserie/index.html">
    <title>Sarikas Bakery Patisserie -</title>
    <section name="Sarikas Bakery PatisserieVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Sarikas Bakery Patisserie 🌐Sarikas Bakery Patisserie 85PW+9X Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85PW+9X Faliraki, Greece Bakery Coffee Birthday Cake Patisserie Sandwich Take Away Breakfast Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/akres-lindos/index.html" source="/listing/akres-lindos/index.html">
    <title>AKRES Lindos -</title>
    <section name="AKRES LindosVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍AKRES Lindos 🌐AKRES Lindos 33RP+67 Lindos, GreeceGet Directions 33RP+67 Lindos, Greece Steak Rooftop Lindos - Pefki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Greek Cuizine - Gourmet No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kisterna-of-eleousa/index.html" source="/listing/kisterna-of-eleousa/index.html">
    <title>Kinsterna of Eleousa -</title>
    <section name="Kinsterna of EleousaVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next A charming spot favored by locals and visitors alike,Kisterna of Eleousaoffers a peaceful retreat under the shade of tall trees and the company of delightful fish. This serene location provides a calming atmosphere perfect for a brief 20-minute visit to unwind and relax. 🔑Funfact During the Italian occupation of Rhodes, the army built a hospital (📍Sanatorium) in the village of Eleousa. Although it was far away from the city, the area has a very mild and pleasant climate, which helped people recovery from chronic illnesses, usually for the treatment of tuberculosis. 📍Kisterna of Eleousa 72FF+6P Eleousa, GreeceGet Directions 72FF+6P Eleousa, Greece Middle Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/gelato-di-bello/index.html" source="/listing/gelato-di-bello/index.html">
    <title>Gelato Di Bello -</title>
    <section name="Gelato Di BelloVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Gelato Di Bello 🌐Gelato Di Bello 7536+JM Kolympia, GreeceGet Directions 7536+JM Kolympia, Greece Crepes Ice Cream waffles Coffee Kolympia - Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+8P Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 75R7+65 Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+W7 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/western-side-of-the-aquarium-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/western-side-of-the-aquarium-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Western Side of the Aquarium - Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Western Side of the Aquarium - RhodesVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Located on the western side of the Aquarium which is located at the northern part of Rhodes, this beach offers some of the most stunning views. The water is clean and refreshingly cold, and despite its proximity to the city center, it remains a tranquil spot. The reason for its relative quietness is the frequent strong winds, sea waves, and the steep drop-off as you enter the water. It's an excellent place to enjoy the waves, with quieter surroundings and more affordable sunbeds compared to Elli Beach. Most of the time, this side of the island experiences waves, but if you visit early in the morning or later in the evening, you’ll usually find it calmer. If you’re not in the mood for swimming in this side of the island, don’t miss an afternoon stroll to watch the breathtaking sunset. It’s a serene way to end the day! 🔑Tip: A handy tip for choosing where to swim is to look at the Greek flag flying above the Aquarium. The direction in which the flag is blowing indicates the side with calmer waters. 📍Western Side of the Aquarium F65C+58, Ρόδος 851 00, ΕλλάδαGet Directions F65C+58, Ρόδος 851 00, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/paradise/index.html" source="/listing/paradise/index.html">
    <title>Paradise -</title>
    <section name="ParadiseVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Paradise 🌐Paradise 7535+VC Kolympia, GreeceGet Directions 7535+VC Kolympia, Greece Kolympia - Afantou Sports Bars No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/traganou-beach-caves/index.html" source="/listing/traganou-beach-caves/index.html">
    <title>Traganou Beach - Caves -</title>
    <section name="Traganou Beach - CavesVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Traganou Beach offers a large, well-organized area with comfortable parking and crystal-clear waters. It’s spacious, so you’ll never feel cramped, and there’s a good taverna nearby for a satisfying meal. However, what truly steals the show are the nearby caves. The large, stunning rocks create a magical landscape. This beach is a favorite among locals for evening swims and celebrations like birthdays, and you'll often find groups of people enjoying the space. 🔑Tips: Stay until sunset to witness the incredible colors as the sky and sea blend.Be cautious as the water deepens suddenly, especially if you have small children. 📍Traganou Beach 📍Traganou Caves ΡΟΔΟΣ ΤΡΑΟΥΝΟΥ ΠΑΡΑΛΙΑ, Καλλιθέα 851 00, ΕλλάδαGet Directions ΡΟΔΟΣ ΤΡΑΟΥΝΟΥ ΠΑΡΑΛΙΑ, Καλλιθέα 851 00, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/oi-spitikes-gefsis-tis-marias/index.html" source="/listing/oi-spitikes-gefsis-tis-marias/index.html">
    <title>Oi Spitikes Gefsis tis Marias -</title>
    <section name="Oi Spitikes Gefsis tis MariasVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Oi Spitikes Gefsis tis Marias 🌐Oi Spitikes Gefsis tis Marias C6G7+W5 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6G7+W5 Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Traditional homemade Greek dishes No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark 85RW+4Q Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes +1Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 86M3+MM Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes +1Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/platea-all-day/index.html" source="/listing/platea-all-day/index.html">
    <title>Platea All Day -</title>
    <section name="Platea All DayVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Platea All Day 🌐Platea All Day 86R3+9C Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86R3+9C Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Brunch Spots No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/yellow-submarine-dive-into-a-unique-adventure/index.html" source="/listing/yellow-submarine-dive-into-a-unique-adventure/index.html">
    <title>Yellow Submarine: Dive into a Unique Adventure! -</title>
    <section name="Yellow Submarine: Dive into a Unique Adventure!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Experience the Yellow Submarine, a large vessel with a glass bottom that lets you see the underwater world while a diver interacts with octopuses and various fish. It's a truly unique experience! As you enjoy the ride, the captain will provide interesting insights about the island of Rhodes. You also have the option to get a souvenir photo for a small extra fee. Definitely a must-do! 📍Yellow Submarine 🌐Yellow Submarine C6XG+V4 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XG+V4 Rhodes, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/lindos-acropolis-of-lindos-lindos-beach/index.html" source="/listing/lindos-acropolis-of-lindos-lindos-beach/index.html">
    <title>Lindos Beach - Acropolis of Lindos - St Paul's Bay Beach -</title>
    <section name="Lindos Beach  - Acropolis of Lindos - St Paul's Bay BeachVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Lindos Beach is always buzzing with life, with its clear waters and plenty of sunbeds where you can just kick back and soak up the sun. There’s a lively vibe, and all around the beach, you’ll find cozy tavernas and cafes where you can enjoy delicious local food. Right above the beach, the Lindos Acropolis sits proudly, offering a view that’ll take your breath away. The ancient ruins are full of history, and the climb up to the top is totally worth it for the stunning views of the island. It’s one of those must-see spots. But if you’re after a bit more peace and quiet, Saint Paul’s Beach is your go-to. It's like a hidden gem—secluded, with crystal-clear waters and a beautiful church sitting on the rocks, creating a vibe you won’t forget. It's the perfect spot to just unwind and take in the surroundings, with a dose of history to top it off. And before you get to Lindos, make sure to stop at that famous viewpoint! You know the one—the stunning view of the Acropolis and the beach. It’s one of those views you’ll want to capture and keep forever. 🔑 Tips: If you plan to visit the Acropolis, try to go early in the morning when it’s cooler. Then, you can spend the rest of the day at the beach! Lindos tends to be a few degrees warmer than the rest of the island, so it’s better to walk around in the afternoon when it’s a bit more comfortable. 📍Lindos 📍Lindos Beach 📍St Paul's Bay Beach 📍Lindos Acropolis 📍Point View Spot ΛΙΝΔΟΣ ΚΡΑΝΑ, Λίνδος 851 07, ΕλλάδαGet Directions ΛΙΝΔΟΣ ΚΡΑΝΑ, Λίνδος 851 07, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/elli-world-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/elli-world-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Elli World Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Elli World RhodesVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Elli World Rhodes 🌐Elli World Rhodes F63F+6W Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F63F+6W Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/pan-vino/index.html" source="/listing/pan-vino/index.html">
    <title>Pan &amp;amp; Vino -</title>
    <section name="Pan &amp;amp; VinoVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Pan &amp;amp; Vino 🌐Pan &amp;amp; Vino C6XC+68 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XC+68 Rhodes, Greece Pasta Pizza Rhodes Town Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/avli/index.html" source="/listing/avli/index.html">
    <title>Avli -</title>
    <section name="AvliVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Avli 🌐Avli C6WF+WQ Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6WF+WQ Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/essential-summer-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/essential-summer-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Essential Summer Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Essential Summer RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Essential Summer Restaurant 🌐Essential Summer Restaurant 85RW+4Q Faliraki, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 85RW+4Q Faliraki, Ελλάδα Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark 7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kato-petres/index.html" source="/listing/kato-petres/index.html">
    <title>Kato Petres -</title>
    <section name="Kato PetresVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Imagine a well-maintained path running alongside a beach, adorned with stunning rocks. As the sun sets, painting the sky, the sound of waves completes this perfect scene. It's real, and it's in Rhodes! 📍Kato Petres 📍Entrance 1 📍Entrance 2 🔑Tips: Best time to visit is late afternoon. Arrive about half an hour before sunset, walk the path, and witness a sky that looks straight out of a dream!Ideal for a relaxing walk, enjoying an ice cream, or even jogging. C6V5+98 Ρόδος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions C6V5+98 Ρόδος, Ελλάδα Rhodes Town Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/stama-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/stama-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Stama Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Stama RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Stama Restaurant 🌐Stama Restaurant 86P5+47 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86P5+47 Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/wine-tasting-in-embonas-a-must-for-wine-lovers/index.html" source="/listing/wine-tasting-in-embonas-a-must-for-wine-lovers/index.html">
    <title>Wine Tasting , A Must for Wine Lovers! -</title>
    <section name="Wine Tasting , A Must for Wine Lovers!Verified listing">Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next If you’re a wine enthusiast, a visit to the village of Embonas is a must! This charming village is home to over 10 wineries, all waiting for you to sample their best wines. Embonas is famous for its hospitable locals, excellent wine, and delicious food. 📌 Mr Local's recommendation: Close to the city . 📍Oeno Culture 🌐Oeno Culture Emponas village . 📍Kounaki Wines 🌐Kounaki Wines 📍Alexandris Family Winery 🌐Alexandris Family Winery 📍MerkourisWinery 🌐Merkouris Winery Cheers to an unforgettable wine-tasting experience! 954V+J2 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 954V+J2 Faliraki, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/spitiki-gonia/index.html" source="/listing/spitiki-gonia/index.html">
    <title>Spitiki Gonia -</title>
    <section name="Spitiki GoniaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Spitiki Gonia 🌐Spitiki Gonia 85QX+9C Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85QX+9C Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/ancient-greek-technology-museum-a-fascinating-journey-through-innovation/index.html" source="/listing/ancient-greek-technology-museum-a-fascinating-journey-through-innovation/index.html">
    <title>Ancient Greek Technology Museum: A Fascinating Journey Through Innovation! -</title>
    <section name="Ancient Greek Technology Museum: A Fascinating Journey Through Innovation!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Prepare to be amazed at the Ancient Greek Technology Museum! Here, you'll discover ingenious mechanisms invented over 2,500 years ago that we still use today. Among the marvels from that era is the manual transmission system for cars (gear box ) , which remains remarkably similar to modern designs. The exhibits are truly impressive, and I’m confident you’ll find them absolutely captivating. 📌Explore more here: 📍Ancient Greek Technology Museum C6VG+P2 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6VG+P2 Rhodes, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/orgettas-bakery/index.html" source="/listing/orgettas-bakery/index.html">
    <title>Orgettas bakery -</title>
    <section name="Orgettas bakeryVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Orgettas bakery 🌐Orgettas bakery 86Q2+WJ Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86Q2+WJ Faliraki, Greece Bakery Coffee Patisserie Sandwich Take Away Breakfast Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C47G+PQ Kremasti Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/jeep-safari-adventure/index.html" source="/listing/jeep-safari-adventure/index.html">
    <title>Jeep Safari Adventure! -</title>
    <section name="Jeep Safari Adventure!Verified listing">Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Drive your own jeep or be a passenger  along as you explore the most famous off-road trails on the island and climb to the highest peak in Rhodes in Atavyros mountain! The experience is truly unique, offering you a chance to learn a lot about Rhodes and discover local restaurants and vineyards. Perfect for all ages! There are plenty of options: Drive your own jeep or opt for a private tour with a 5-seater jeep.Choose a larger jeep with 10+ seats for group adventures.📌 Mr Local's recommendation: For self-drive and private tours, we recommend 🌐Bumpy Rhodes Safaris. 📍Bumpy Rhodes Safaris For guided group tours: 🌐Daktari Island Safari 📍Daktari Island Safari With fantastic guide Michalis. Definitely a must-do! 86W2+3G Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86W2+3G Faliraki, Greece C6PG+4J Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6PG+4J Rhodes, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/7-springs/index.html" source="/listing/7-springs/index.html">
    <title>7 Springs  -</title>
    <section name="7 SpringsVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Located in a lush natural setting, 7 Springs is another hidden gem in Rhodes! To reach the waterfall and the serene lake, you can take a nearly 150-meter tunnel, originally built by the Italians, with a stream running through it! 🔑Tips: 📍Visit the springs Explore the surrounding area Walk through the tunnel Admire the lake Enjoy the waterfall On your way back, savor a delicious meal or a refreshing drink at the nearby 📍Restaurant. 7437+5C Archangelos, GreeceGet Directions 7437+5C Archangelos, Greece Middle Rhodes Kolympia - Afantou Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kallithea-springs-a-destination-straight-out-of-paradise-2/index.html" source="/listing/kallithea-springs-a-destination-straight-out-of-paradise-2/index.html">
    <title>Kallithea Springs: A destination straight out of paradise! -</title>
    <section name="Kallithea Springs: A destination straight out of paradise!Verified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Although I don't usually like to use the word "must," if you're visiting Rhodes, you HAVE to check out Kallithea Springs. Located 9 km from Rhodes Town, this unique blend of nature, architecture, and history offers a truly special experience! The Kallithea Springs have been renowned for their therapeutic properties since ancient times and the Knights' era. Enhancement of the springs began in 1927, with their waters being mixed with other therapeutic sources, and the facilities were completed in 1929. The clear, vibrant sea and Italian-inspired decor will leave you amazed! Perfect for both a swim and an evening outing. 🔑Tips Explore the entire area.Enjoy the stunning views and vibrant atmosphere. 📍Kallithea Springs📍Themes of Kallithea📍Kallithea Springs Seaside 96HP+3W Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 96HP+3W Rhodes, Greece No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/monastery-of-the-virgin-mary-of-tsambika-kyra-psili/index.html" source="/listing/monastery-of-the-virgin-mary-of-tsambika-kyra-psili/index.html">
    <title>Monastery of the Virgin Mary of Tsambika (Kyra Psili) -</title>
    <section name="Monastery of the Virgin Mary of Tsambika (Kyra Psili)Verified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next This historicmonastery,perched on a hill with breathtaking views, is rich in local legend. According to tradition, an icon of the Virgin Mary mysteriously disappeared from Cyprus and reappeared on the hill in Rhodes several times, leading to the construction of the monastery in her honor. Another story tells of a woman who, after swallowing a wick given by a nun, miraculously conceived a child. Many couples still visit the monastery, praying for the blessing of children and often naming their offspring Tsampikos or Tsampika after the miracle. 📍Monastery of the Virgin Mary of Tsambika (Kyra Psili) 🔑Tips: Wear athletic shoes and bring water and a snack to climb up 300 steps. Rest stops with benches are available along the way. 64PX+8R Archangelos, GreeceGet Directions 64PX+8R Archangelos, Greece Stegna - Archangelos Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/quad-safari-adventure-2/index.html" source="/listing/quad-safari-adventure-2/index.html">
    <title>Quad Safari Adventure! -</title>
    <section name="Quad Safari Adventure!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Rhodes isn’t just about stunning beaches; it also boasts beautiful mountains and forests! Exploring these with a car can be challenging, but if you’re riding a quad and have a good co-pilot, the experience becomes truly unforgettable! Discover hidden island paths you never knew existed and take in some breathtaking mountain views that are simply incredible! The adventure usually lasts 2-3 hours and is perfect for all ages! If you love off-road driving, trust me, the quad safari is made for you! 📌 Mr Local's recommendation: 📍Faliraki Quad Safariwith guide and leader Petros! It was amazing! 86P2+GW Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86P2+GW Faliraki, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/stegna-gorgona-fish-taverna/index.html" source="/listing/stegna-gorgona-fish-taverna/index.html">
    <title>STEGNA GORGONA FISH TAVERNA -</title>
    <section name="STEGNA GORGONA FISH TAVERNAVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍STEGNA GORGONA FISH TAVERNA 🌐STEGNA GORGONA FISH TAVERNA 646R+RH Stegna, GreeceGet Directions 646R+RH Stegna, Greece Stegna - Archangelos Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/food-gate/index.html" source="/listing/food-gate/index.html">
    <title>Food Gate -</title>
    <section name="Food GateVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Food Gate 🌐Food Gate C6J7+W9 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6J7+W9 Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Burger Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/villa-de-vecchi-mussolinis-villa/index.html" source="/listing/villa-de-vecchi-mussolinis-villa/index.html">
    <title>Villa de Vecchi (Mussolini's Villa) -</title>
    <section name="Villa de Vecchi (Mussolini's Villa)Verified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Villa de Vecchiis perched on Profitis Elias mountain. This villa, built between 1936 and 1947 by Mussolini's adviser Count Cesare de Vecchi, was intended as Mussolini's summer residence, though he never stayed there. The villa, facing the Elafos and Elafina Hotel, showcases alpine-style architecture, part of the fascist dictator's plan to make Rhodes an Italian outpost. Remarkably, the villa's original chapel and stained glass windows remain intact, while the French doors in the living room frame stunning views over the Turkish coast and Symi Island. Surrounded by lush forests, the journey to the villa is as enjoyable as the destination! 🔑Tips: Wear comfortable athletic shoes during your visit. Always carry water with you. The best time to visit is in the morning. Don’t forget to enjoy a coffee with a wonderful view and try some local sweets! 7WGV+C8 Profitis Ilias, GreeceGet Directions 7WGV+C8 Profitis Ilias, Greece Middle Rhodes South Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/cactus-restaurant-faliraki/index.html" source="/listing/cactus-restaurant-faliraki/index.html">
    <title>Cactus Restaurant Faliraki -</title>
    <section name="Cactus Restaurant FalirakiVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Cactus Restaurant Faliraki 🌐Cactus Restaurant Faliraki 86Q3+8Q Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86Q3+8Q Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Brunch Spots No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/taverna-anthoula/index.html" source="/listing/taverna-anthoula/index.html">
    <title>Taverna Anthoula -</title>
    <section name="Taverna AnthoulaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Taverna Anthoula 🌐Taverna Anthoula 745R+GP Archangelos, GreeceGet Directions 745R+GP Archangelos, Greece Kolympia - Afantou Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/golden-fish-sushi-chinese-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/golden-fish-sushi-chinese-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Golden Fish Sushi &amp;amp; Chinese Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Golden Fish Sushi &amp;amp; Chinese RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Golden Fish Sushi &amp;amp; Chinese Restaurant 🌐Golden Fish Sushi &amp;amp; Chinese Restaurant C59H+9X Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C59H+9X Ialysos, Greece Ialysos Ixia Asian and Korean cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C5HX+CP Ialysos Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C47M+WC Kremasti Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6X8+VV Rhodes Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/southern-beaches-of-rhodes-west-side/index.html" source="/listing/southern-beaches-of-rhodes-west-side/index.html">
    <title>Southern Beaches of Rhodes - West Side -</title>
    <section name="Southern Beaches of Rhodes - West SideVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Some beaches on the west side of the island, particularly in the southern part, are truly remarkable. Here are a few noteworthy ones: 📍Kamiros Beach A pristine beach with clear waters, ideal for a peaceful day by the sea. It's a great spot for swimming and relaxing. 📍Fournoi Beach A beautiful and quiet beach, perfect for nature lovers. The untouched beauty of this beach makes it a must-visit in southern Rhodes.These beaches are ideal for those seeking a more laid-back and natural beach experience in Rhodes. 📍Κopria Beach Kopria Beach stands out for its wild, authentic landscape and serene environment, far from the busy tourist spots. It is an excellent choice for those who appreciate quiet beaches with clean waters and a laid-back vibe. 4P4P+JP Ατάβυρος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 4P4P+JP Ατάβυρος, Ελλάδα 8WV8+34 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 8WV8+34 Rhodes, Greece 7RC9+V7 Ατάβυρος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 7RC9+V7 Ατάβυρος, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/alkionis-sports-bar-grill/index.html" source="/listing/alkionis-sports-bar-grill/index.html">
    <title>Alkionis Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill -</title>
    <section name="Alkionis Sports Bar &amp;amp; GrillVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Alkionis Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill 🌐Alkionis Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill C5C4+5P Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C5C4+5P Ialysos, Greece Ixia Ialysos Sports Bars No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/butterflies-valley-a-natural-wonderland/index.html" source="/listing/butterflies-valley-a-natural-wonderland/index.html">
    <title>Butterflies’ Valley: A Natural Wonderland -</title>
    <section name="Butterflies’ Valley: A Natural WonderlandVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Immerse yourself in the lush greenery of theButterflies’ Valley, where you’ll encounter small waterfalls, babbling brooks, and towering trees teeming with butterflies. The best time to visit is from June to September when the valley is most vibrant with these delicate creatures. 📍Butterflies Valley 🔑Tips: During your visit, avoid making noise as the butterflies get scared, and in their attempt to fly away, they hit their wings against the rocks! Wear comfortable athletic shoes for a pleasant walk. After exploring, enjoy a refreshing drink or snack at the nearby taverna. 83Q5+VV Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 83Q5+VV Rhodes, Greece Middle Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/canton-kremasti/index.html" source="/listing/canton-kremasti/index.html">
    <title>Canton Kremasti -</title>
    <section name="Canton KremastiVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Canton Kremasti 🌐Canton Kremasti C47M+WC Kremasti, GreeceGet Directions C47M+WC Kremasti, Greece Kremasti Ialysos Ixia Asian and Korean cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C5HX+CP Ialysos Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6X8+VV Rhodes Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark 85QX+PQ Faliraki Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/tulip-toulipa-patisserie/index.html" source="/listing/tulip-toulipa-patisserie/index.html">
    <title>Toulipa - Tulip Patisserie -</title>
    <section name="Toulipa - Tulip  PatisserieVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Toulipa - Tulip Patisserie 🌐Toulipa - Tulip Patisserie C6X9+Q9 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6X9+Q9 Rhodes, Greece Patisserie Birthday Cake Rhodes Town Must-Visit Patisseries No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6MG+PJ Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C6PG+GM Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C47G+JG Kremasti Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/mela-karamela/index.html" source="/listing/mela-karamela/index.html">
    <title>Mela Karamela -</title>
    <section name="Mela KaramelaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Mela Karamela 🌐Mela Karamela 94PP+MM Pastida, GreeceGet Directions 94PP+MM Pastida, Greece Birthday Cake Patisserie Kremasti Must-Visit Patisseries No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6MG+PJ Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C6PG+GM Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C47G+JG Kremasti Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kontiki-next/index.html" source="/listing/kontiki-next/index.html">
    <title>Kontiki NEXT -</title>
    <section name="Kontiki NEXTVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Kontiki NEXT 🌐Kontiki NEXT C6XG+6X Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XG+6X Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Brunch Spots No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/sala-pietra-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/sala-pietra-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Sala Pietra Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Sala Pietra RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Sala Pietra Restaurant 🌐Sala Pietra Restaurant 86C3+C4 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 86C3+C4 Rhodes, Greece Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Restaurants - Bars Traditional homemade Greek dishes No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/grande-blue-beach-the-instagram-worthy-paradise/index.html" source="/listing/grande-blue-beach-the-instagram-worthy-paradise/index.html">
    <title>Grande Blue Beach: The Instagram-Worthy Paradise -</title>
    <section name="Grande Blue Beach: The Instagram-Worthy ParadiseVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Grande Blue Beach is a must-visit gem on Rhodes, perfect for those who love stunning scenery and crystal-clear waters. To reach this small paradise, you’ll need to pass by Stegna BeachThe beach offers immaculate waters that are ideal for swimming and relaxing. The area is well-organized and always kept clean, with a good beach bar offering great prices and quality products. To the left of the main beach, you’ll find a charming private beach and a magical cave. The cave is a special attraction, but be cautious as the path to it is rocky. Find it here 📍Grande Blue beach 📍Magic Caves 🔑 Tips:Footwear: Wear athletic shoes for the rocky path to ensure safety and comfort.Safety: Be cautious of the rocky terrain around the cave. 642R+GG Αρχάγγελος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 642R+GG Αρχάγγελος, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/pitafan-yeeros-ialissos/index.html" source="/listing/pitafan-yeeros-ialissos/index.html">
    <title>Pitafan Yeeros Ialissos -</title>
    <section name="Pitafan Yeeros IalissosVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Pitafan Yeeros Ialissos 🌐Pitafan Yeeros Ialissos C58F+VG Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C58F+VG Ialysos, Greece Ialysos Ixia Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/porto-antico/index.html" source="/listing/porto-antico/index.html">
    <title>Porto Antico -</title>
    <section name="Porto AnticoVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Porto Antico 🌐Porto Antico 8WR8+F9 Kameiros, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 8WR8+F9 Kameiros, Ελλάδα Western Rhodes Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/koumparaki-2/index.html" source="/listing/koumparaki-2/index.html">
    <title>KoumpaRáki -</title>
    <section name="KoumpaRákiVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍KoumpaRáki 🌐KoumpaRáki F628+GH Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F628+GH Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/noble-gourmet-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/noble-gourmet-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Noble Gourmet Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Noble Gourmet RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Noble Gourmet Restaurant 🌐Noble Gourmet Restaurant 96CF+XX Ammoudes, GreeceGet Directions 96CF+XX Ammoudes, Greece Steak Faliraki Kallithea Greek Cuizine - Gourmet Greek Cuisine - Restaurant No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/sergios-downtown/index.html" source="/listing/sergios-downtown/index.html">
    <title>Sergio’s Downtown -</title>
    <section name="Sergio’s DowntownVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Sergio’s Downtown 🌐Sergio’s Downtown C6XF+3C Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XF+3C Rhodes, Greece Pasta Pizza Rhodes Town Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C5C5+99 Ialysos Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/jim-nolis/index.html" source="/listing/jim-nolis/index.html">
    <title>Jim &amp;amp; Nolis -</title>
    <section name="Jim &amp;amp; NolisVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Jim &amp;amp; Nolis 🌐Jim &amp;amp; Nolis 86Q2+8P Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86Q2+8P Faliraki, Greece Ice Cream Crepes waffles Take Away Breakfast Coffee Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">75R7+65 Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+W7 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86V2+32 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/colossus-of-rhodes-harbor-landmarks/index.html" source="/listing/colossus-of-rhodes-harbor-landmarks/index.html">
    <title>Colossus of Rhodes &amp;amp; Harbor Landmarks -</title>
    <section name="Colossus of Rhodes &amp;amp; Harbor LandmarksVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next At the harbor entrance, where the famous Colossus of Rhodes (one of the seven wonders of the ancient world) once stood, you now find the deer statues. Opposite them are the Saint Nicholas fortress and the windmills. 🔑Tips: Take a stroll around the area, especially in the late afternoon for the best experience! Visit the Deer statues, the road to Saint Nicholas fortress, and the windmills. 📍Deer Statues 📍Saint Nicholas Fortress 📍Rhodes Windmills</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/rialto-la-spritzeria/index.html" source="/listing/rialto-la-spritzeria/index.html">
    <title>RIALTO LA SPRITZERIA -</title>
    <section name="RIALTO LA SPRITZERIAVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍RIALTO LA SPRITZERIA 🌐RIALTO LA SPRITZERIA C6XC+8M Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XC+8M Rhodes, Greece Pasta Pizza Rhodes Town Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C5C5+99 Ialysos Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/agathi-beach-golden-sand/index.html" source="/listing/agathi-beach-golden-sand/index.html">
    <title>Agathi Beach - Golden sand -</title>
    <section name="Agathi Beach - Golden sandVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Agathi Beach is often considered the most beautiful and unspoiled beach on Rhodes, free from human intervention. The beach boasts golden-red sand and crystal-clear waters, creating a stunning natural setting. Since it is unorganized, it’s essential to bring your own umbrella for shade, as well as sunscreen. If you plan to stay for several hours, it's wise to bring water and snacks. The shallow waters make it ideal for families with small children, while nature lovers will be enchanted by the pristine environment. 📍Agathi Beach 53GX+G7 Αρχάγγελος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 53GX+G7 Αρχάγγελος, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/haraki-dreams-restaurant-bar/index.html" source="/listing/haraki-dreams-restaurant-bar/index.html">
    <title>Haraki Dreams Restaurant Bar -</title>
    <section name="Haraki Dreams Restaurant BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Haraki Dreams Restaurant Bar 🌐Haraki Dreams Restaurant Bar 538V+MF, Χαράκι 851 02, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 538V+MF, Χαράκι 851 02, Ελλάδα Charaki Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/felicia-ristorante/index.html" source="/listing/felicia-ristorante/index.html">
    <title>Felicia Ristorante -</title>
    <section name="Felicia RistoranteVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Felicia Ristorante 🌐Felicia Ristorante C6HM+RG Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6HM+RG Rhodes, Greece Pasta Pizza Rhodes Town Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/mimakos-taverna/index.html" source="/listing/mimakos-taverna/index.html">
    <title>Mimakos Taverna - Greek Night -</title>
    <section name="Mimakos Taverna - Greek NightVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Mimakos Taverna 🌐Mimakos Taverna 854H+P8 Kallithea, GreeceGet Directions 854H+P8 Kallithea, Greece Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/%ce%b7-%ce%b1%cf%80%cf%8c%ce%bb%ce%b1%cf%85%cf%83%ce%b7-%cf%84%ce%bf%cf%85-%cf%83%cf%84%ce%ad%cf%81%ce%b3%ce%bf%cf%85-i-apolafsi-tou-stergou/index.html" source="/listing/%ce%b7-%ce%b1%cf%80%cf%8c%ce%bb%ce%b1%cf%85%cf%83%ce%b7-%cf%84%ce%bf%cf%85-%cf%83%cf%84%ce%ad%cf%81%ce%b3%ce%bf%cf%85-i-apolafsi-tou-stergou/index.html">
    <title>Η Απόλαυση (του Στέργου) - I Apolafsi tou stergou -</title>
    <section name="Η Απόλαυση (του Στέργου) - I Apolafsi tou stergouVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Η Απόλαυση (του Στέργου) - I Apolafsi tou stergou 🌐Η Απόλαυση (του Στέργου) - I Apolafsi tou stergou 8WQX+W7, Καλαβάρδα 851 06, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 8WQX+W7, Καλαβάρδα 851 06, Ελλάδα Western Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/bliss-cocktail-shisha-bar/index.html" source="/listing/bliss-cocktail-shisha-bar/index.html">
    <title>Bliss Cocktail &amp;amp; Shisha Bar -</title>
    <section name="Bliss Cocktail &amp;amp; Shisha BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Bliss Cocktail &amp;amp; Shisha Bar 🌐Bliss Cocktail &amp;amp; Shisha Bar 86R2+X4 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86R2+X4 Faliraki, Greece Shisha Pizza Pasta Faliraki Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/happy-friends/index.html" source="/listing/happy-friends/index.html">
    <title>Happy Friends -</title>
    <section name="Happy FriendsVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Happy Friends 🌐Happy Friends 33F4+Q3 Pefki, GreeceGet Directions 33F4+Q3 Pefki, Greece Lindos - Pefki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Brunch Spots Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/star-fast-food/index.html" source="/listing/star-fast-food/index.html">
    <title>STAR FAST FOOD -</title>
    <section name="STAR FAST FOODVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍STAR FAST FOOD 🌐STAR FAST FOOD 85VX+4X Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85VX+4X Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/pavo-cafe/index.html" source="/listing/pavo-cafe/index.html">
    <title>Pavo Cafe -</title>
    <section name="Pavo CafeVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Pavo Cafe 🌐Pavo Cafe 86G2+9R Καλλιθέα, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 86G2+9R Καλλιθέα, Ελλάδα Faliraki Brunch Spots No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/taverna-yiarenis/index.html" source="/listing/taverna-yiarenis/index.html">
    <title>Taverna Yiarenis -</title>
    <section name="Taverna YiarenisVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Taverna Yiarenis 🌐Taverna Yiarenis 7X68+54 Apollona, GreeceGet Directions 7X68+54 Apollona, Greece Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/rodini-park/index.html" source="/listing/rodini-park/index.html">
    <title>Rodini Park -</title>
    <section name="Rodini ParkVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next A green paradise! Rumored to be the oldest park in the world, it's "hidden" beneath tall trees, with bridges and ponds filled with water lilies, alongside a natural stream. Ducks and peacocks are now the park's "permanent" residents. A relaxing walk and a bit of exploration will enchant you. The area stays cool thanks to the tall trees. 📍Rodini Park 🔑Tips: Visit in the morning; the sunlight makes it magical! Bring water with you. You can bring some bread to feed the ducks and peacocks! C6GC+Q4 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6GC+Q4 Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/restaurant-taverna-pigi-fasouli/index.html" source="/listing/restaurant-taverna-pigi-fasouli/index.html">
    <title>Restaurant-Taverna Pigi Fasouli -</title>
    <section name="Restaurant-Taverna Pigi FasouliVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Restaurant-Taverna Pigi Fasouli 🌐Restaurant-Taverna Pigi Fasouli 836W+WW Καλλιθέα, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 836W+WW Καλλιθέα, Ελλάδα Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/fish-restaurant-plimmiri/index.html" source="/listing/fish-restaurant-plimmiri/index.html">
    <title>Fish Restaurant Plimmiri -</title>
    <section name="Fish Restaurant PlimmiriVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Fish Restaurant Plimmiri 🌐Fish Restaurant Plimmiri WVH5+MF Plimmiri, GreeceGet Directions WVH5+MF Plimmiri, Greece South Rhodes Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/enidrio-aquarium-or-elli-beach/index.html" source="/listing/enidrio-aquarium-or-elli-beach/index.html">
    <title>Enidrio (Aquarium) or Elli Beach -</title>
    <section name="Enidrio (Aquarium) or Elli BeachVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next The stretch of beach from the Aquarium (tip of the island) to the Elli beach bar is known as Enidrio (Aquarium) or Elli beach among locals. This beach is the most famous beach in the center of Rhodes, and it’s easy to see why. With deep, cool, and crystal-clear waters, this beach is in the heart of the city, just a stone's throw from the Medieval Town of Rhodes. The colorful umbrellas, beach bars, restaurants, towering hotels, Casino of Rodos, and the Rhodes Aquarium create a picturesque scene that has become iconic, often featured on cult postcards. This beach caters to all ages and is full of life, offering everything you might need for a perfect day by the sea. Along the beach, you’ll find people playing tennis or beach volleyball, with the most famous spot being the trampoline! A massive concrete diving board with three different heights for diving, located in the middle of the sea but easily reachable by swimming. Built during the Italian occupation, it remains a favorite among locals and visitors alike. Elli Beach is also known for its vibrant underwater life, so don't forget to bring a mask and explore the lively seabed. Don't forget to go parasailing! The view is incredible! 📍Gabriels Watersports The owners and the staff are very helpful. 📍Elli Beach F63F+FM Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F63F+FM Rhodes, Greece No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/koutouki-42-2/index.html" source="/listing/koutouki-42-2/index.html">
    <title>Koutouki 42 -</title>
    <section name="Koutouki 42Verified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Koutouki 42 🌐Koutouki 42 F638+2Q Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F638+2Q Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/savazio/index.html" source="/listing/savazio/index.html">
    <title>Savazio -</title>
    <section name="SavazioVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Savazio 🌐Savazio C6MG+PJ Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6MG+PJ Rhodes, Greece Patisserie Birthday Cake Rhodes Town Must-Visit Patisseries No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6PG+GM Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C47G+JG Kremasti Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark 94PP+MM Pastida Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/johnnys-pub/index.html" source="/listing/johnnys-pub/index.html">
    <title>Johnny's Pub -</title>
    <section name="Johnny's PubVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Johnny's Pub 🌐Johnny's Pub F62C+VM Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F62C+VM Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Sports Bars No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/to-stolidi-tis-psinthou/index.html" source="/listing/to-stolidi-tis-psinthou/index.html">
    <title>To Stolidi tis Psinthou -</title>
    <section name="To Stolidi tis PsinthouVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍To Stolidi tis Psinthou 🌐To Stolidi tis Psinthou 837W+P5 Ψινθος, GreeceGet Directions 837W+P5 Ψινθος, Greece Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/1947-the-greek-mixology-bar/index.html" source="/listing/1947-the-greek-mixology-bar/index.html">
    <title>1947 - The Greek Mixology Bar -</title>
    <section name="1947 - The Greek Mixology BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍1947 - The Greek Mixology Bar 🌐1947 - The Greek Mixology Bar 86Q2+F7 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86Q2+F7 Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/to-posperi/index.html" source="/listing/to-posperi/index.html">
    <title>To Posperi -</title>
    <section name="To PosperiVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍To Posperi 🌐To Posperi C575+W2 Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C575+W2 Ialysos, Greece Ialysos Ixia Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/limeri-traditional-guesthouse-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/limeri-traditional-guesthouse-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Limeri Traditional Guesthouse &amp;amp; Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Limeri Traditional Guesthouse &amp;amp; RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Limeri Traditional Guesthouse &amp;amp; Restaurant 🌐Limeri Traditional Guesthouse &amp;amp; Restaurant 4PJQ+42 Monolithos, GreeceGet Directions 4PJQ+42 Monolithos, Greece South Rhodes Western Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/porto-bello/index.html" source="/listing/porto-bello/index.html">
    <title>Porto Bello -</title>
    <section name="Porto BelloVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Porto Bello 🌐Porto Bello 86Q3+WQ Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86Q3+WQ Faliraki, Greece Pasta Pizza Faliraki Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/masa-taverna/index.html" source="/listing/masa-taverna/index.html">
    <title>Masa Taverna -</title>
    <section name="Masa TavernaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Masa Taverna 🌐Masa Taverna 86M3+MM Faliraki, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 86M3+MM Faliraki, Ελλάδα Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark 7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/steki-fast-food/index.html" source="/listing/steki-fast-food/index.html">
    <title>Steki Fast Food -</title>
    <section name="Steki Fast FoodVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Steki Fast Food 🌐Steki Fast Food C6WG+W2 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6WG+W2 Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/homu-sushi-bar-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/homu-sushi-bar-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Homu Sushi Bar - Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Homu Sushi Bar - RhodesVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Homu Sushi Bar - Rhodes 🌐Homu Sushi Bar - Rhodes C6X8+VV Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6X8+VV Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Asian and Korean cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C5HX+CP Ialysos Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C47M+WC Kremasti Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark 85QX+PQ Faliraki Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/costa-mare/index.html" source="/listing/costa-mare/index.html">
    <title>Costa Mare -</title>
    <section name="Costa MareVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Costa Mare 🌐Costa Mare C5F6+29 Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C5F6+29 Ialysos, Greece Steak Ialysos Ixia Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/gyro-burger/index.html" source="/listing/gyro-burger/index.html">
    <title>Gyro &amp;amp; Burger -</title>
    <section name="Gyro &amp;amp; BurgerVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Gyro &amp;amp; Burger 🌐Gyro &amp;amp; Burger 75R7+54 Afantou, GreeceGet Directions 75R7+54 Afantou, Greece Kolympia - Afantou Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/archaeological-site-of-kamiros/index.html" source="/listing/archaeological-site-of-kamiros/index.html">
    <title>Archaeological Site of Kamiros -</title>
    <section name="Archaeological Site of KamirosVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next 📍Kamirosis a city with a history spanning over 3,000 years! In ancient times, Kamiros, along with Ialyssos and Lindos, were the three major cities of Rhodes. The site’s remarkable findings offer a glimpse into the life of the civilization that once thrived here! 🔑Tips: Due to the island’s high temperatures, the best times to visit are early in the morning or late in the afternoon (check the visiting hours). Make sure to carry water with you! 8WPC+8H Kameiros, GreeceGet Directions 8WPC+8H Kameiros, Greece Western Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kallithea-springs-a-destination-straight-out-of-paradise/index.html" source="/listing/kallithea-springs-a-destination-straight-out-of-paradise/index.html">
    <title>Kallithea Springs: A destination straight out of paradise! -</title>
    <section name="Kallithea Springs: A destination straight out of paradise!Verified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Although I don't usually like to use the word "must," if you're visiting Rhodes, you HAVE to check out Kallithea Springs. Located 9 km from Rhodes Town, this unique blend of nature, architecture, and history offers a truly special experience! The Kallithea Springs have been renowned for their therapeutic properties since ancient times and the Knights' era. Enhancement of the springs began in 1927, with their waters being mixed with other therapeutic sources, and the facilities were completed in 1929. The clear, vibrant sea and Italian-inspired decor will leave you amazed! Perfect for both a swim and an evening outing. 🔑Tips Explore the entire area.Enjoy the stunning views and vibrant atmosphere. 📍Kallithea Springs📍Themes of Kallithea📍Kallithea Springs Seaside 96HP+3W Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 96HP+3W Rhodes, Greece Faliraki Kallithea Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/manolis-taverna/index.html" source="/listing/manolis-taverna/index.html">
    <title>Manolis Taverna -</title>
    <section name="Manolis TavernaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Manolis Taverna 🌐Manolis Taverna 86P2+RH Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86P2+RH Faliraki, Greece Steak Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/coffeeday/index.html" source="/listing/coffeeday/index.html">
    <title>COFFEEDAY -</title>
    <section name="COFFEEDAYVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍COFFEEDAY 🌐COFFEEDAY C47G+PQ Kremasti, GreeceGet Directions C47G+PQ Kremasti, Greece Coffee Bakery Sandwich Take Away Breakfast Kremasti Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/a-hidden-gem-in-south-rhodes-perfect-beachside-dining/index.html" source="/listing/a-hidden-gem-in-south-rhodes-perfect-beachside-dining/index.html">
    <title>A Hidden Gem in South Rhodes: Perfect Beachside Dining -</title>
    <section name="A Hidden Gem in South Rhodes: Perfect Beachside DiningVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next A Hidden Gem in South Rhodes: Perfect Beachside DiningNestled along a beautiful beach in South Rhodes, this restaurant is a true gem. With its stunning location and breathtaking views of the endless blue sea and sky, it's the perfect spot to enjoy a delicious meal after a swim or to savor a romantic dinner away from the hustle and bustle of the city! A must-visit for anyone exploring the area! 📍Votsalo Restaurant &amp;amp; Beach Bar WVXF+4H Lachania, GreeceGet Directions WVXF+4H Lachania, Greece No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/scuba-diving-discover-the-underwater-magic-of-rhodes-2/index.html" source="/listing/scuba-diving-discover-the-underwater-magic-of-rhodes-2/index.html">
    <title>Scuba Diving: Discover the Underwater Magic of Rhodes! -</title>
    <section name="Scuba Diving: Discover the Underwater Magic of Rhodes!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Just as vibrant as Rhodes is on land, its underwater world is equally alive with wonders! Explore seas teeming with life, intriguing shipwrecks, and magical underwater spots. Programs are available for all skill levels, complete with top-notch training that makes the experience truly enchanting. 📌 Mr Local's recommendation: 📍BigFishDive in Faliraki. Panagiotis provided fantastic lessons, and my group and I were absolutely thrilled with the experience. An absolute must! 86V2+R9 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86V2+R9 Faliraki, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/mandomata-beach-a-nudists-paradise/index.html" source="/listing/mandomata-beach-a-nudists-paradise/index.html">
    <title>Mandomata Beach: A Nudist's Paradise -</title>
    <section name="Mandomata Beach: A Nudist's ParadiseVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Mandomata Beach is a well-known nudist beach where you can enjoy the freedom of naturism. This organized beach has everything you need for a comfortable visit. It features a sandy shoreline and is well-equipped for sunbathing and swimming. Do note that there are some rocks in the water, so a bit of caution is advised. If naturism is your thing, this beach is perfect for you. Find it here 📍Mandomata Beach Apollonos 1, Φαληράκι 851 00, ΕλλάδαGet Directions Apollonos 1, Φαληράκι 851 00, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kapetanios-sea-food-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/kapetanios-sea-food-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Kapetanios Sea food Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Kapetanios Sea food RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Kapetanios Sea food Restaurant 🌐Kapetanios Sea food Restaurant 539W+2J, Χαράκι 851 02, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 539W+2J, Χαράκι 851 02, Ελλάδα Charaki Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/am-the-coffee-shop/index.html" source="/listing/am-the-coffee-shop/index.html">
    <title>am: The Coffee Shop -</title>
    <section name="am: The Coffee ShopVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍am: The Coffee Shop 🌐am: The Coffee Shop C66G+PG Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C66G+PG Rhodes, Greece Bakery Coffee Sandwich Take Away Breakfast Kallithea Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/explore-rhodes-on-foot-discover-hidden-gems/index.html" source="/listing/explore-rhodes-on-foot-discover-hidden-gems/index.html">
    <title>Explore Rhodes on Foot: Discover Hidden Gems! -</title>
    <section name="Explore Rhodes on Foot: Discover Hidden Gems!Verified listing">Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next You don’t always need to spend money to enjoy an activity. Sometimes, a walk can be the best adventure! In Rhodes, many amazing spots reveal their charm in the late afternoon. Here are some fantastic walking routes to consider: From the Rhodes Aquarium to Ixia via Kato Petres: Enjoy a scenic walk from the Rhodes Aquarium to Ixia, passing by the beautiful Kato Petres. The late afternoon views are simply breathtaking! 📍Rhodes Aquarium 📍Kato Petres 📍Ixia Visit the Small Port of Faliraki and the Church of the Holy Apostles: Enjoy a stroll around the charming port of Faliraki and take in the stunning view of Faliraki Beach from the Church of the Holy Apostles. 📍Faliraki Port 📍Church of the Holy Apostles Walk the Moat in the Old Town: Explore the historic moat surrounding Rhodes’ Old Town for a step back in time. 📍Old Town Moat Enjoy these walks and soak in the local beauty and history of Rhodes! C6V5+88 Ρόδος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions C6V5+88 Ρόδος, Ελλάδα Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/eteon-greek-culture-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/eteon-greek-culture-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>ETEON Greek Culture Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="ETEON Greek Culture RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍ETEON Greek culture restaurant 🌐ETEON Greek culture restaurant 86W2+7C Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86W2+7C Faliraki, Greece Steak Faliraki Greek Cuizine - Gourmet Greek Cuisine - Restaurant No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/agrino/index.html" source="/listing/agrino/index.html">
    <title>Agrino -</title>
    <section name="AgrinoVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Agrino 🌐Agrino C6J8+8Q Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6J8+8Q Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/golden-wok/index.html" source="/listing/golden-wok/index.html">
    <title>Golden Wok -</title>
    <section name="Golden WokVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Golden Wok 🌐Golden Wok 85QX+PQ Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85QX+PQ Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Asian and Korean cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C5HX+CP Ialysos Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C47M+WC Kremasti Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6X8+VV Rhodes Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/dream-cream/index.html" source="/listing/dream-cream/index.html">
    <title>Dream Cream -</title>
    <section name="Dream CreamVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Dream Cream 📍Dream Cream 🌐Dream Cream F62C+G6 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F62C+G6 Rhodes, Greece Ice Cream Crepes waffles Coffee Rhodes Town Ialysos Ixia Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+8P Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 75R7+65 Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+W7 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/gyro-gyro-oloi/index.html" source="/listing/gyro-gyro-oloi/index.html">
    <title>Gyro Gyro Oloi -</title>
    <section name="Gyro Gyro OloiVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Gyro Gyro Oloi 🌐Gyro Gyro Oloi 6478+8C Archangelos, GreeceGet Directions 6478+8C Archangelos, Greece Stegna - Archangelos Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/mousikorama-3/index.html" source="/listing/mousikorama-3/index.html">
    <title>Mousikorama -</title>
    <section name="MousikoramaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Mousikorama 🌐Mousikorama 85XW+M9 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 85XW+M9 Rhodes, Greece Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/farma-of-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/farma-of-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Farma Of Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Farma Of RhodesVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Enjoy playing, feeding, walking, and taking photos with adorable animals! Thefarmis spacious, clean, and offers a unique interaction with the animals, making it a memorable experience for both kids and adults. 📍Farma Of Rhodes 🔑Tips: Wear good shoes, as there's a lot of walking, but it's worth every step. Urchase food at the entrance to feed the animals; it’s sure to make you smile and laugh! If you're still unsure, just take a look at some photos and you'll be convinced! 923W+5R, Επάνω Καλαμωνας 851 06, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 923W+5R, Επάνω Καλαμωνας 851 06, Ελλάδα Middle Rhodes South Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kapari-fish-sea/index.html" source="/listing/kapari-fish-sea/index.html">
    <title>Kapari Fish &amp;amp; Sea -</title>
    <section name="Kapari Fish &amp;amp; SeaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Kapari Fish &amp;amp; Sea 🌐Kapari Fish &amp;amp; Sea 7539+JX Kolympia, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 7539+JX Kolympia, Ελλάδα Kolympia - Afantou Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/ladiko-bay-a-crystal-clear-gem/index.html" source="/listing/ladiko-bay-a-crystal-clear-gem/index.html">
    <title>Ladiko Bay: A Crystal-Clear Gem -</title>
    <section name="Ladiko Bay: A Crystal-Clear GemVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Ladiko Bay is renowned for its stunning, crystal-clear waters and beautiful beach. This organized spot is one of the island's most famous beaches, and it’s easy to see why! 🔑 Tips: The sea has some rocky areas, so it’s a good idea to wear water shoes or be a bit careful.Bring a snorkel mask! The underwater life is vibrant and worth exploring!Find it here 📍Ladiko Bay 📍Ladiko Restaurant Beach Bar: Located right on the beach, this restaurant offers friendly and efficient service, reasonable prices, and has been a local favorite for over 50 years. They must be doing something right! 📍Sala Pietra RestaurantΑuthentic Greek hospitality , authentic Greek cuisine, homemade dishes, beautiful decor, and amazing cocktails. At night, the place takes on a magical atmosphere! 86C4+63 Καλλιθέα, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 86C4+63 Καλλιθέα, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/gastronomy-tour-an-authentic-experience/index.html" source="/listing/gastronomy-tour-an-authentic-experience/index.html">
    <title>Gastronomy Tour: An Authentic Experience! -</title>
    <section name="Gastronomy Tour: An Authentic Experience!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Experience it by yourself!Experience the charm of Chatzidiakou Farm, where interacting with animals is truly unique. Gather fresh eggs from the hens, pick vegetables from the garden, and collect milk straight from the farm. You'll also learn traditional local traditional recipes that highlight the farm's bounty. 📌Find out more on theirFacebook page. The owners are incredibly kind and welcoming. 📍Chatzidiakou farm - gastronomy tour 84GX+Q7 Kalithies, GreeceGet Directions 84GX+Q7 Kalithies, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/nodo-burgers/index.html" source="/listing/nodo-burgers/index.html">
    <title>Nodo burgers -</title>
    <section name="Nodo burgersVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Nodo burgers 🌐Nodo burgers 86R3+CC Faliraki, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 86R3+CC Faliraki, Ελλάδα Faliraki Burger Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/marco-polo/index.html" source="/listing/marco-polo/index.html">
    <title>Marco Polo -</title>
    <section name="Marco PoloVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Marco Polo 🌐Marco Polo C6VG+58 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6VG+58 Rhodes, Greece Steak Rhodes Old Town Greek Cuisine - Restaurant No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/dionysos-restaurant-lindos/index.html" source="/listing/dionysos-restaurant-lindos/index.html">
    <title>Dionysos Restaurant - Lindos -</title>
    <section name="Dionysos Restaurant - LindosVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Dionysos Restaurant - Lindos 🌐Dionysos Restaurant - Lindos 33RP+CG Lindos, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 33RP+CG Lindos, Ελλάδα Rooftop Steak Lindos - Pefki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/meze-meze/index.html" source="/listing/meze-meze/index.html">
    <title>Meze Meze -</title>
    <section name="Meze MezeVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Meze Meze 🌐Meze Meze 86X3+J9 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86X3+J9 Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/al-hayat-resto-bar-2/index.html" source="/listing/al-hayat-resto-bar-2/index.html">
    <title>Al Hayat Resto Bar -</title>
    <section name="Al Hayat Resto BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Al Hayat Resto Bar 🌐Al Hayat Resto Bar C6PQ+M4 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6PQ+M4 Rhodes, Greece Shisha Pasta Pizza Rhodes Town Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+F7 Faliraki Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/old-town-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/old-town-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Old Town Rhodes - Medieval City Of Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Old Town Rhodes - Medieval City Of RhodesVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Explore both the inside and outside ofRhodes'📍Old Town, where highlights include: 📍Street of the Knights 📍Palace of the Grand Master 📍Hippocrates Square 📍Square  Evreon Martiron 📍Socrates Street 📍Gate of Saint Athanasius 📍Gate of the Cannons 📍Venetian Clock Tower 📍Medieval Town Moat 🔑Tips: Start early in the morning to fully immerse yourself in the narrow, winding streets. For an unforgettable experience, enjoy the sunset with an ice cream from "SKALAKIA" the stairs behind the fountain in Hippocrates Square as the sun sets behind the high walls, painting the sky with stunning colors! Always ask for a menu at any bar or restaurant you visit to avoid surprises. C6VH+V2 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6VH+V2 Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Old Town Rhodes Town Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/a-culinary-adventure/index.html" source="/listing/a-culinary-adventure/index.html">
    <title>A Culinary Adventure! -</title>
    <section name="A Culinary Adventure!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next For those who love cooking and want to dive into the island's flavors, the Rhodes Cooking Class is a perfect choice! Here, you’ll learn local recipes and uncover the secrets behind them from passionate locals who truly love the traditional cuisine and their island. In our delicious dishes, there’s a special ingredient called "Meraki," which means putting your heart and soul into what you do. This cooking class will show you exactly how it works! 📌Explore more here: 📍Rhodes Cooking Class 🌐Rhodes Cooking Class 64P9+23 Archangelos, GreeceGet Directions 64P9+23 Archangelos, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/ktima-lindos/index.html" source="/listing/ktima-lindos/index.html">
    <title>Ktima Lindos -</title>
    <section name="Ktima LindosVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Ktima Lindos 🌐Ktima Lindos Ρόδου - Λίνδου, 851 07 Lindos, GreeceGet Directions Ρόδου - Λίνδου, 851 07 Lindos, Greece Steak Lindos - Pefki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/beerokouto/index.html" source="/listing/beerokouto/index.html">
    <title>Beerõkouto -</title>
    <section name="BeerõkoutoVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Beerõkouto 🌐Beerõkouto C6VG+PQ Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6VG+PQ Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Old Town Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/monastery-of-saint-george-apollakia-village/index.html" source="/listing/monastery-of-saint-george-apollakia-village/index.html">
    <title>Monastery of Saint George (Apollakia Village) -</title>
    <section name="Monastery of Saint George (Apollakia Village)Verified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Another hidden gem with breathtaking views! TheMonastery of Saint Georgeis situated in a stunning spot where the lush green of the trees meets the deep blue of the sea, and the sun dances with the sky. 📍Monastery of Saint George 🔑Tips: Visit near sunset for the most spectacular view, as the sun sets from this side of the island. Drive cautiously as the road is narrow with limited visibility.Grab some takeaway food or pack a picnic and drinks to enjoy a romantic sunset with your partner. Your partner might just love you a little bit more for it! 3QM9+RJ Nótia Ródos, GreeceGet Directions 3QM9+RJ Nótia Ródos, Greece Middle Rhodes South Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/tsambika-beach/index.html" source="/listing/tsambika-beach/index.html">
    <title>Tsambika Beach! -</title>
    <section name="Tsambika Beach!Verified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next A large, organized sandy beach with crystal-clear waters, ideal for families with small children due to its shallow waters. The shoreline offers everything you need, from a water park and watersports to beach bars and restaurants. Worth a visit! 🔑Tips Be careful with the parking. Some areas have sand, and the car might get stuck! Don't forget to take a photo with the Greek flag painted on the rock! 📍Tsampika Beach 📍Greek flag 64JX+G8 Αρχάγγελος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 64JX+G8 Αρχάγγελος, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/artisti-di-gelato/index.html" source="/listing/artisti-di-gelato/index.html">
    <title>Artisti di Gelato -</title>
    <section name="Artisti di GelatoVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Artisti di Gelato 🌐Artisti di Gelato 75R7+65 Afantou, GreeceGet Directions 75R7+65 Afantou, Greece Ice Cream Crepes waffles Kolympia - Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+8P Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+W7 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86V2+32 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/memories-cocktails-and-sports-bar/index.html" source="/listing/memories-cocktails-and-sports-bar/index.html">
    <title>Memories Cocktails and Sports Bar -</title>
    <section name="Memories Cocktails and Sports BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Memories Cocktails and Sports Bar 🌐Memories Cocktails and Sports Bar 7537+98 Kolympia, GreeceGet Directions 7537+98 Kolympia, Greece Kolympia - Afantou Sports Bars No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kamina-shisha-cafe-bar/index.html" source="/listing/kamina-shisha-cafe-bar/index.html">
    <title>Kamina Shisha Cafe Bar -</title>
    <section name="Kamina Shisha Cafe BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Kamina Shisha Cafe Bar 🌐Kamina Shisha Cafe Bar 85MX+RH Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85MX+RH Faliraki, Greece Shisha Faliraki Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/ristorante-pizzeria-rosso-di-sera/index.html" source="/listing/ristorante-pizzeria-rosso-di-sera/index.html">
    <title>Ristorante Pizzeria "Rosso di Sera" -</title>
    <section name="Ristorante Pizzeria &quot;Rosso di Sera&quot;Verified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Ristorante Pizzeria "Rosso di Sera" 🌐Ristorante Pizzeria "Rosso di Sera" 7528+58 Kolympia, GreeceGet Directions 7528+58 Kolympia, Greece Pasta Pizza Kolympia - Afantou Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/oasis-beach-kallithea-a-vibrant-beach-bar-experience/index.html" source="/listing/oasis-beach-kallithea-a-vibrant-beach-bar-experience/index.html">
    <title>Oasis Beach, Kallithea: A Vibrant Beach Bar Experience -</title>
    <section name="Oasis Beach, Kallithea: A Vibrant Beach Bar ExperienceVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Oasis Beach in Kallithea is one of the most beautiful beach bars in Rhodes! The owners clearly love the place, and it shows! You can easily spend an entire day here without missing a thing. The beach features clear, deep waters full of life, and the underwater scenery is stunning. A snorkeling mask is a must to fully appreciate the vibrant marine life. The area is rocky, so a bit of caution is advised if you have small children. Occasionally, they host some of the biggest beach parties in Rhodes, with announcements made on their Instagram page: 📍Oasis Beach Bar. 🌐Oasis Beach Bar 96FP+X4 Kallithea, GreeceGet Directions 96FP+X4 Kallithea, Greece No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/seafood-limanaki-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/seafood-limanaki-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Seafood Limanaki Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Seafood Limanaki RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Seafood Limanaki Restaurant 🌐Seafood Limanaki Restaurant 7528+2M, Κολύμπια 851 02, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 7528+2M, Κολύμπια 851 02, Ελλάδα Kolympia - Afantou Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/boston-burger-bar-2/index.html" source="/listing/boston-burger-bar-2/index.html">
    <title>Boston Burger bar -</title>
    <section name="Boston Burger barVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Boston Burger bar 🌐Boston Burger bar C6WF+VM Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6WF+VM Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Burger Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/nightlife-in-rhodes-2/index.html" source="/listing/nightlife-in-rhodes-2/index.html">
    <title>Nightlife In Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Nightlife In RhodesVerified listing">Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next The island has a vibrant nightlife during the summer months.Mainly, there are three bar streets on the island , and many of night clubs . There's one rule:Wherever you like, you go in 😎 📍Orfanidou Bar Street 📍Faliraki Bar Street 📍Kolympia Bar Street And the 📍Old Townis one of the liveliest spots for nightlife! Some of the most famous clubs are located on these streets : 📍Evripidou Street 📍Menekleous Street and a personal favorite  choice because of the music they play : 📍Route bar In Rhodes Town, you’ll also find an open-air nightclub that hosts events with famous DJs. In the past,  Artbat, Steve Aoki, and Miss Monique have performed there! 📍NOR Beach House Project Noteworthy are also two clubs in the beautiful Lindos : 📍Arches Plus Open Air Club 📍Amphitheatre Night Club F63G+58 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F63G+58 Rhodes, Greece Nightlife In Rhodes No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/casa-italia-pizza-pasta-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/casa-italia-pizza-pasta-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Casa Italia Pizza &amp;amp; Pasta Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Casa Italia Pizza &amp;amp; Pasta RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Casa Italia pizza &amp;amp; pasta Restaurant 🌐Casa Italia pizza &amp;amp; pasta Restaurant C5C4+P7 Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C5C4+P7 Ialysos, Greece Pasta Pizza Ialysos Ixia Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/maintanos-kremidi/index.html" source="/listing/maintanos-kremidi/index.html">
    <title>Maintanos Kremidi -</title>
    <section name="Maintanos KremidiVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Maintanos Kremidi 🌐Maintanos Kremidi C6JM+C5 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6JM+C5 Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/original-burger-house/index.html" source="/listing/original-burger-house/index.html">
    <title>Original Burger House -</title>
    <section name="Original Burger HouseVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Original Burger House 🌐Original Burger House C6C4+7W Sgourou, GreeceGet Directions C6C4+7W Sgourou, Greece Rhodes Town Burger Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/perigiali-sea-food-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/perigiali-sea-food-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Perigiali Sea Food Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Perigiali Sea Food RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Perigiali Sea Food Restaurant 🌐Perigiali Sea Food Restaurant 643R+83 Archangelos, GreeceGet Directions 643R+83 Archangelos, Greece Stegna - Archangelos Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/symi-island-worth-visit/index.html" source="/listing/symi-island-worth-visit/index.html">
    <title>Symi Island - Worth Visit ! -</title>
    <section name="Symi Island - Worth Visit !Verified listing">Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Symi is a magical island full of color and charm. Stroll along the beautiful harbor in Gialos, then walk up the famous Kali Strata steps to the old town and the historic Castle for amazing views. Visit the peaceful Panormitis Monastery by the sea and learn about local life at the Archaeological and Folklore Museum. And don’t forget to relax at Agios Georgios Dysalonas beach, where the clear blue water and high cliffs will take your breath away. 📍Panormitis Monastery 📍Symi Harbor 📍Kali Strata 📍Venetian Castle of Symi 📍Archaeological &amp;amp; Folklore Museum of Symi 📍Saint George bayThere is no road access, so visitors can only reach it by boat, adding to its untouched charm. During the summer season, it's very easy to get from Rhodes (📍Mandraki Harbor) to Symi—there are daily ferries, with plenty of boats and departure times to choose from. Our recommendation is : 🌐Rhodes Sea Lineswith different cruise options for every taste. 🌐Dodekanisos Seaways C6XG+87 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XG+87 Rhodes, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/stegna-beach-a-picturesque-escape-in-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/stegna-beach-a-picturesque-escape-in-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Stegna Beach: A Picturesque Escape in Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Stegna Beach: A Picturesque Escape in RhodesVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next 📍Stegna Beachfeels like a hidden gem from another island, maintaining its authentic island charm untouched by time. This picturesque spot is divided into two beaches, each offering a serene escape. With its traditional tavernas lining the shore, you’re in for a culinary treat, it's hard to be disappointed no matter where you choose to dine. However, some stand out for their exceptional offerings: 📌 Mr Local's recommendation: 📍Stegna Kozas📍Gorgona Seafood Restaurant📍Perigiali Sea Food Restaurant αρχαγγελοσ ροδοσ, Στεγνά 851 02, ΕλλάδαGet Directions αρχαγγελοσ ροδοσ, Στεγνά 851 02, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/thomas-pub/index.html" source="/listing/thomas-pub/index.html">
    <title>Thomas Pub -</title>
    <section name="Thomas PubVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Thomas Pub 🌐Thomas Pub 85PW+HH Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85PW+HH Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Sports Bars No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/del-angelo-pizza-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/del-angelo-pizza-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Del Angelo Pizza Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Del Angelo Pizza RhodesVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Del Angelo Pizza Rhodes 🌐Del Angelo Pizza Rhodes C584+QJ Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C584+QJ Ialysos, Greece Pasta Pizza Ixia Ialysos Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/pane-di-capo/index.html" source="/listing/pane-di-capo/index.html">
    <title>Pane di Capo -</title>
    <section name="Pane di CapoVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Pane di Capo 🌐Pane di Capo C47G+JG Kremasti, GreeceGet Directions C47G+JG Kremasti, Greece Patisserie Bakery Coffee Birthday Cake Kremasti Ialysos Must-Visit Patisseries No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6MG+PJ Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C6PG+GM Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark 94PP+MM Pastida Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/charaki-beach/index.html" source="/listing/charaki-beach/index.html">
    <title>Charaki Beach -</title>
    <section name="Charaki BeachVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next A picturesque beach on the island with perfect waters. The locals are incredibly welcoming and kind, giving the place a very positive vibe. Visiting once a month feels like therapy for the soul. The local restaurants are exceptional, with a couple of personal favorites. 📍Charaki Beach 📌 Mr Local's recommendations: 📍Haraki Dreams Restaurant Bar Delicious dishes and the friendliest staff! 📍Kapetanios Seafood Restaurant Nearby, with equally tasty food and a smiling team. 539W+2J, Χαράκι 851 02, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 539W+2J, Χαράκι 851 02, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/solo-gelato-faliraki/index.html" source="/listing/solo-gelato-faliraki/index.html">
    <title>Solo Gelato Faliraki -</title>
    <section name="Solo Gelato FalirakiVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Solo Gelato Faliraki 🌐Solo Gelato Faliraki 86V2+32 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86V2+32 Faliraki, Greece Ice Cream Crepes waffles Coffee Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+8P Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 75R7+65 Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+W7 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/pizzeria-pomodoro/index.html" source="/listing/pizzeria-pomodoro/index.html">
    <title>Pizzeria Pomodoro -</title>
    <section name="Pizzeria PomodoroVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Pizzeria Pomodoro 🌐Pizzeria Pomodoro 86Q2+FC Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86Q2+FC Faliraki, Greece Pasta Pizza Faliraki Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C5C5+99 Ialysos Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/anika-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/anika-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Anika Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Anika RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Anika Restaurant 🌐Anika Restaurant 85QW+WM Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85QW+WM Faliraki, Greece Steak Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/general-sandwich-bar/index.html" source="/listing/general-sandwich-bar/index.html">
    <title>General Sandwich Bar -</title>
    <section name="General Sandwich BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍General Sandwich Bar 🌐General Sandwich Bar C6WG+W3 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6WG+W3 Rhodes, Greece Take Away Breakfast Rhodes Town Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/cavo-tango-sushi-cocktail-bar/index.html" source="/listing/cavo-tango-sushi-cocktail-bar/index.html">
    <title>Cavo Tango Sushi Cocktail Bar -</title>
    <section name="Cavo Tango Sushi Cocktail BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Cavo Tango Sushi Cocktail Bar 🌐Cavo Tango Sushi Cocktail Bar C5C3+QW Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C5C3+QW Ialysos, Greece Shisha Steak Ialysos Ixia Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/tsoukka-%ce%bc%ce%b1%ce%b3%ce%b5%ce%b9%cf%81%ce%b5%ce%af%ce%bf%ce%bd/index.html" source="/listing/tsoukka-%ce%bc%ce%b1%ce%b3%ce%b5%ce%b9%cf%81%ce%b5%ce%af%ce%bf%ce%bd/index.html">
    <title>Tsoukka μαγειρείον -</title>
    <section name="Tsoukka μαγειρείονVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Tsoukka μαγειρείον 🌐Tsoukka μαγειρείον 85PX+97 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85PX+97 Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark 85RW+4Q Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes +1Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 86M3+MM Faliraki Traditional homemade Greek dishes +1Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/maroullakis-taverna/index.html" source="/listing/maroullakis-taverna/index.html">
    <title>Maroullakis Taverna -</title>
    <section name="Maroullakis TavernaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Maroullakis Taverna 🌐Maroullakis Taverna 6VG3+WX Embonas, GreeceGet Directions 6VG3+WX Embonas, Greece South Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/lindos-acropolis-of-lindos/index.html" source="/listing/lindos-acropolis-of-lindos/index.html">
    <title>Lindos Village - Acropolis of Lindos -</title>
    <section name="Lindos Village - Acropolis of LindosVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Lindos is one of the three ancient cities of Rhodes, offering a unique charm that sets it apart. The Acropolis of Lindos, with its ancient ruins, narrow streets, stunning beaches, and picturesque restaurants, is simply breathtaking. The village is adorned with traditional white and blue buildings, making it one of the most scenic spots on the island. This is a place you must visit, with the Acropolis being the cherry on top. The crystal-clear waters of all the beaches are perfect, so no matter which one you choose, you won’t be disappointed. However, one beach, in particular, offers an incredible view with the Acropolis in the background, making it a standout choice. 📍Lindos Village 📍Lindos Acropolis 📍Lindos PointView 🔑Tips: Visit in the early morning to avoid the crowds and extreme heat, especially from June to August. Avoid driving down the steep hill expecting to find parking; it's better to park earlier and walk down. Spend an entire day here—from morning till evening. The beauty and experience are unmatched. For a photo opportunity, make sure to visit this Spot. 33RJ+2X Λίνδος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 33RJ+2X Λίνδος, Ελλάδα Lindos - Pefki South Rhodes Middle Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/memphis-restaurant-bbq-grill/index.html" source="/listing/memphis-restaurant-bbq-grill/index.html">
    <title>Memphis Restaurant BBQ Grill -</title>
    <section name="Memphis Restaurant BBQ GrillVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Memphis Restaurant BBQ Grill 🌐Memphis Restaurant BBQ Grill F63C+5J Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F63C+5J Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Burger Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/village-taste/index.html" source="/listing/village-taste/index.html">
    <title>Village taste -</title>
    <section name="Village tasteVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Village taste 🌐Village taste 86P2+7W Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86P2+7W Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/amethystos-gastronomy-meze-bar/index.html" source="/listing/amethystos-gastronomy-meze-bar/index.html">
    <title>Amethystos Gastronomy Meze Bar -</title>
    <section name="Amethystos Gastronomy Meze BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Amethystos Gastronomy Meze Bar 🌐Amethystos Gastronomy Meze Bar 6478+7H Archangelos, GreeceGet Directions 6478+7H Archangelos, Greece Stegna - Archangelos Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kritinia-castle-a-timeless-view/index.html" source="/listing/kritinia-castle-a-timeless-view/index.html">
    <title>Kritinia Castle: A Timeless View -</title>
    <section name="Kritinia Castle: A Timeless ViewVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next This 500-year-oldcastle, worn by battles and time, stands in a stunning location. While the castle itself may not offer much in terms of historical detail, the breathtaking views alone make it worth a visit. 📍Kritinia Castle 🔑Tips: The best time to visit is in the afternoon when the setting sun illuminates the castle, creating a magical scene. Bring water with you. 7R75+JH Siana, GreeceGet Directions 7R75+JH Siana, Greece Middle Rhodes Western Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/anthony-quinn-bay/index.html" source="/listing/anthony-quinn-bay/index.html">
    <title>Anthony Quinn Bay - The Most Famous Beach -</title>
    <section name="Anthony Quinn Bay - The Most Famous BeachVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next A landmark beach on the island! It’s a spot you must visit in Rhodes and spend a beautiful morning. No matter how many times I’ve been, I can never get enough of it! The water is always clean and refreshingly cool. The seabed is teeming with fish, making for an incredible underwater view. 🔑Tips: Visit before 10:30 AM to secure a good spot, especially during June, July, and August when it gets quite crowded.Bring a snorkel mask to experience the amazing underwater world.Enjoy the coldest beer in a fantastic atmosphere!📌 Mr Local's recommendations: 📍Kounna Beach &amp;amp; Resto Bar: The highlight of the beach! Who wouldn’t want to dine with such a view? The food quality is five-star as well. 📍The Greek Bush: The crown jewel of the beach. 86C5+GC Καλλιθέα, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 86C5+GC Καλλιθέα, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/mythos-bakery-cafe/index.html" source="/listing/mythos-bakery-cafe/index.html">
    <title>Mythos Bakery Cafe -</title>
    <section name="Mythos Bakery CafeVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Mythos Bakery Cafe 🌐Mythos Bakery Cafe 85PX+W6 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85PX+W6 Faliraki, Greece Bakery Crepes Coffee Take Away Breakfast Sandwich Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/villa-di-mare-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/villa-di-mare-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Villa Di Mare Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Villa Di Mare RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Villa Di Mare Restaurant🌐Villa Di Mare Restaurant C59M+R4 Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C59M+R4 Ialysos, Greece Steak Ialysos Ixia Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/pasatempos/index.html" source="/listing/pasatempos/index.html">
    <title>Pasatempos -</title>
    <section name="PasatemposVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Pasatempos 🌐Pasatempos 9469+PH Maritsa, GreeceGet Directions 9469+PH Maritsa, Greece Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/il-borgo-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/il-borgo-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Il Borgo Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Il Borgo RhodesVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Il Borgo Rhodes 🌐Il Borgo Rhodes C6VJ+66 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6VJ+66 Rhodes, Greece Pasta Pizza Rhodes Old Town Italian Cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6XC+8M Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6XF+3C Rhodes Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark 86Q2+FC Faliraki Italian Cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/whispers/index.html" source="/listing/whispers/index.html">
    <title>Whispers -</title>
    <section name="WhispersVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Whispers 🌐Whispers C589+Q2 Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C589+Q2 Ialysos, Greece Steak Ialysos Ixia Greek Cuisine - Restaurant No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6JP+XR Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant Quick view Bookmark 85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/mezedopoleio-masasoura/index.html" source="/listing/mezedopoleio-masasoura/index.html">
    <title>Mezedopoleio Masasoura -</title>
    <section name="Mezedopoleio MasasouraVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Mezedopoleio Masasoura 🌐Mezedopoleio Masasoura 9458+RP Maritsa, GreeceGet Directions 9458+RP Maritsa, Greece Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/pier-rhodes-new-marina/index.html" source="/listing/pier-rhodes-new-marina/index.html">
    <title>Pier Rhodes New Marina -</title>
    <section name="Pier Rhodes New MarinaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍PIER food*cafe 🌐PIER food*cafe C6MQ+67 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6MQ+67 Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Brunch Spots No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/nami-sushi-korean-bbq/index.html" source="/listing/nami-sushi-korean-bbq/index.html">
    <title>Nami Sushi &amp;amp; Korean BBQ -</title>
    <section name="Nami Sushi &amp;amp; Korean BBQVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Nami Sushi &amp;amp; Korean BBQ 🌐Nami Sushi &amp;amp; Korean BBQ C5HX+CP Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C5HX+CP Ialysos, Greece Ialysos Ixia Asian and Korean cuisine No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C47M+WC Kremasti Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark C6X8+VV Rhodes Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark 85QX+PQ Faliraki Asian and Korean cuisine Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/tiffanys-cafe-bistro/index.html" source="/listing/tiffanys-cafe-bistro/index.html">
    <title>Tiffany's Cafe &amp;amp; Bistro -</title>
    <section name="Tiffany's Cafe &amp;amp; BistroVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Tiffany's Cafe &amp;amp; Bistro 🌐Tiffany's Cafe &amp;amp; Bistro 85XW+Q9 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85XW+Q9 Faliraki, Greece Coffee Sandwich Take Away Breakfast Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/filerimos/index.html" source="/listing/filerimos/index.html">
    <title>Filerimos - Filerimos Cross -</title>
    <section name="Filerimos - Filerimos CrossVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next This was once the site of the Acropolis of Ialyssos, one of the three major ancient cities of Rhodes. You can still find the foundations of the Doric Temple of Athena and Zeus. The area is rich in history and offers many exploration opportunities, with a scenic route that leads to breathtaking panoramic views. Walk alongside beautiful peacocks, visit the cross for a stunning view, and explore the nearby church! 📍Filerimos 📍Filerimos Cross 🔑Tips: The entrance to the mountain closes at sunset, so plan your visit just before sunset to enjoy the view. Bring a camera and your sense of adventure! If you're staying in Ialysos and love uphill jogging, the Filerimos mountain is the perfect challenge. However, make sure to go early in the morning to avoid the sun! 94XW+M2 Ialisos, GreeceGet Directions 94XW+M2 Ialisos, Greece Ialysos Ixia Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/pagotomania-gelato-cafe/index.html" source="/listing/pagotomania-gelato-cafe/index.html">
    <title>Pagotomania Gelato Cafe -</title>
    <section name="Pagotomania Gelato CafeVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Pagotomania Gelato Cafe 🌐Pagotomania Gelato Cafe 86Q3+W7 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86Q3+W7 Faliraki, Greece Ice Cream Crepes waffles Coffee Birthday Cake Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+8P Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 75R7+65 Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86V2+32 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/monolithos-castle-spectacular-sunset-views/index.html" source="/listing/monolithos-castle-spectacular-sunset-views/index.html">
    <title>Monolithos Castle: Spectacular Sunset Views -</title>
    <section name="Monolithos Castle: Spectacular Sunset ViewsVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Perched on a rock 500 years old,Monolithos Castleoffers arguably the most beautiful sunset view on Rhodes!  At over 200 meters above the sea, the castle provides an unrivaled panorama of lush greenery and endless ocean. 📍Monolithos Castle 🔑Tips: Visit early in the morning or late in the afternoon to avoid the heat. If visiting in the evening, stay until sunset for an unforgettable view. Bring water, a camera, and be prepared for a view you'll remember for a lifetime! Don't forget to try the local products from the kiosk before the castle. Made with love by the locals! 4PFG+RC Monolithos, GreeceGet Directions 4PFG+RC Monolithos, Greece South Rhodes Western Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/koulourades-ialysos/index.html" source="/listing/koulourades-ialysos/index.html">
    <title>Koulourades Ialysos -</title>
    <section name="Koulourades IalysosVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Koulourades Ialysos 🌐Koulourades Ialysos C584+H9 Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C584+H9 Ialysos, Greece Bakery Sandwich Take Away Breakfast Coffee Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/zucchero-by-haris/index.html" source="/listing/zucchero-by-haris/index.html">
    <title>Zucchero by Haris -</title>
    <section name="Zucchero by HarisVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Zucchero by Haris 🌐Zucchero by Haris 4374+6Q Λίνδος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 4374+6Q Λίνδος, Ελλάδα Bakery Birthday Cake Crepes Ice Cream Patisserie Take Away Breakfast Sandwich Lindos - Pefki Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C47G+PQ Kremasti Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/mavros-kavos-beach/index.html" source="/listing/mavros-kavos-beach/index.html">
    <title>Mavros Kavos Beach -</title>
    <section name="Mavros Kavos BeachVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Mavros Kavos is the most beautiful hidden beach in Rhodes! This pristine beach features clean sand and crystal-clear waters. Nature lovers will fall in love with this secluded spot. However, reaching it isn't easy, and driving requires caution. If you encounter sand on the road, it's best to continue on foot as your car might get stuck. This destination demands good physical fitness, so come prepared. Be sure to bring an umbrella for shade, along with water and food, as you'll truly be on your own here. A perfect escape for those seeking solitude. 📍Mavros kavos Beach WR26+WM Νότια Ρόδος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions WR26+WM Νότια Ρόδος, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/sunset-beach-horseback-riding-a-magical-experience-2/index.html" source="/listing/sunset-beach-horseback-riding-a-magical-experience-2/index.html">
    <title>Sunset Beach Horseback Riding: A Magical Experience! -</title>
    <section name="Sunset Beach Horseback Riding: A Magical Experience!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Experience the magic of horseback riding with a breathtaking sunset view by the sea! No special Mr Local's recommendations are needed. The title says it all! Just immerse yourself in the experience; the scenery and emotions are truly unique! 📌 Mr Local's recommendation: 📍NiVa Ranch Horse Riding Rhodes C429+V9 Kremasti, GreeceGet Directions C429+V9 Kremasti, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/tsalmidis-bakery-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/tsalmidis-bakery-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Tsalmidis Bakery Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Tsalmidis Bakery RhodesVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Tsalmidis Bakery Rhodes 🌐Tsalmidis Bakery Rhodes C6G4+7J Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6G4+7J Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Must-Visit Patisseries No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6MG+PJ Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C6PG+GM Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C47G+JG Kremasti Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/bridges-taverna/index.html" source="/listing/bridges-taverna/index.html">
    <title>Bridges Taverna -</title>
    <section name="Bridges TavernaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Bridges Taverna 🌐Bridges Taverna 85QW+9X Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85QW+9X Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/urban-burger-bar-2/index.html" source="/listing/urban-burger-bar-2/index.html">
    <title>Urban Burger Bar -</title>
    <section name="Urban Burger BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Urban Burger Bar 🌐Urban Burger Bar C6XF+2C Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6XF+2C Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Burger Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/molos-restaurant/index.html" source="/listing/molos-restaurant/index.html">
    <title>Molos Restaurant -</title>
    <section name="Molos RestaurantVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Molos Restaurant 🌐Molos Restaurant 3293+WM Lardos, GreeceGet Directions 3293+WM Lardos, Greece South Rhodes Middle Rhodes Lindos - Pefki Fish Taverna No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/academy-billiards-and-sports-bar-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/academy-billiards-and-sports-bar-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Academy Billiards and Sports Bar Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Academy Billiards and Sports Bar RhodesVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Academy Billiards and Sports Bar Rhodes 🌐Academy Billiards and Sports Bar Rhodes C6QP+CC Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6QP+CC Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Sports Bars No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/faliraki-beach-the-ultimate-beach-destination/index.html" source="/listing/faliraki-beach-the-ultimate-beach-destination/index.html">
    <title>Faliraki Beach: The Ultimate Beach Destination -</title>
    <section name="Faliraki Beach: The Ultimate Beach DestinationVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next 📍Faliraki Beach The stretch of beach from Faliraki Harbor to the Naya Beach Bar is known as Faliraki Beach among locals. Faliraki Beach is the go-to spot for everything you might want in a beach experience! Stretching over 4.5 km, it has it all! Beach bars, restaurants, taverns, and lively parties. Whether you’re looking for a vibrant atmosphere or a relaxing spot, Faliraki Beach caters to all! 📌 Mr Local's recommendations: Beach Bars &amp;amp; Restaurants: 📍Galazio Restaurant &amp;amp; Beach Bar- The perfect balance. 📍Aquarius Beach Bar- you'll find everything here! 📍Naya Beach Bar &amp;amp; Restaurant- A popular spot with great food and ambiance. 📍Tulum Beach Bar Restaurant- Perfect for a fun evening with music and excellent food. Family-Friendly Areas: For a quieter experience, visit the beaches from the Faliraki harbor to Beach Bar Chaplins. Watersports: Faliraki Beach is ideal for watersports enthusiasts. 📍Sotos Watersportand 📍Peter’s Aqua Sport Cluboffer a range of activities and are two of the best clubs in the island.For speedboat rentals without a licence,📍Manolis Speed Boatswith 20 years experience is the best choice! For renting boats with a captain or private cruises, i would recommend 📍Rock My Boat Faliraki - Boat Rentals - Private Cruises For a unique experience, try jet skiing with 📍Faliraki Watersports (Kostas). Dining Options: For a variety of dining experiences, try: 📍Porto Bello 📍Taverna Stefanos 📍Monaxia Taverna Bar It doesn’t really matter where you choose to eat or drink, as I’ve never been disappointed by any of the places! 86R3+7C Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 86R3+7C Rhodes, Greece No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/gala-seaside-kitchen-bar/index.html" source="/listing/gala-seaside-kitchen-bar/index.html">
    <title>Gala Seaside Kitchen + Bar -</title>
    <section name="Gala Seaside Kitchen + BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Gala Seaside Kitchen + Bar 🌐Gala Seaside Kitchen + Bar 86Q3+CQ Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86Q3+CQ Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Brunch Spots No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/iceart-gelateria/index.html" source="/listing/iceart-gelateria/index.html">
    <title>IceART - Gelateria -</title>
    <section name="IceART - GelateriaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍IceART - Gelateria 🌐IceART - Gelateria C6X9+JQ Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6X9+JQ Rhodes, Greece Crepes Ice Cream waffles Rhodes Town Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+8P Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 75R7+65 Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+W7 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/taverna-perama/index.html" source="/listing/taverna-perama/index.html">
    <title>Taverna Perama -</title>
    <section name="Taverna PeramaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Taverna Perama 🌐Taverna Perama 7259+7Q Platania, GreeceGet Directions 7259+7Q Platania, Greece Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/prasonisi-prasonisi-lighthouse/index.html" source="/listing/prasonisi-prasonisi-lighthouse/index.html">
    <title>Prasonisi - Prasonisi Lighthouse -</title>
    <section name="Prasonisi - Prasonisi LighthouseVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Prasonisi is located at the southernmost tip of Rhodes, where nature has created a stunning landscape! The islet is connected to the mainland by a strip of sand, forming two exotic sandy beaches that change shape depending on the season and weather conditions. Due to favorable winds, this area is a favorite destination for kitesurfers and windsurfers from all around the world! 📍Prasonisi Beach As you pass the main beach and head towards Prasonisi, there is a hidden beach worth visiting! At the end of the islet, you'll find the famous Prasonisi Lighthouse, offering a unique and breathtaking view. 🔑Tips: Visit the hidden beach with a companion for safety.The area offers amazing views and is perfect for photography. For the best views and photos at Prasonisi, there are a few must-visit spots:📍Viewpoint for Photos 📍Stone Attraction 📍Hidden beach 📍Prasonisi Lighthouse VQQF+WG Πρασονήσι, ΕλλάδαGet Directions VQQF+WG Πρασονήσι, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kathara-beach-faliraki-perfect-for-families/index.html" source="/listing/kathara-beach-faliraki-perfect-for-families/index.html">
    <title>Kathara Beach - Faliraki: Perfect for Families -</title>
    <section name="Kathara Beach - Faliraki: Perfect for FamiliesVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Kathara Beach in Faliraki is a family-friendly destination with its sandy shores and shallow waters. It’s a popular spot for locals, especially on Sundays when many families bring their children for a relaxing day out. While Rhodes offers many beautiful beaches, Kathara Beach stands out for those seeking tranquility and a safe environment for kids. Find it here 📍Kathara Beach 📌 Mr Local's recommendation Dining Options Near Kathara Beach Enjoy a delightful meal with fresh, local flavors at 📍Taverna Cavos 📍Stama Restaurant. 📍Victoria Beach Restaurant Perfect for a beachside meal or a cocktail! 86M5+R7 Φαληράκι, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 86M5+R7 Φαληράκι, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/glory-days-fbi-sports-bar-and-grill/index.html" source="/listing/glory-days-fbi-sports-bar-and-grill/index.html">
    <title>Glory Days FBI - Sports Bar and Grill -</title>
    <section name="Glory Days FBI - Sports Bar and GrillVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Glory Days FBI - Sports Bar and Grill 🌐Glory Days FBI - Sports Bar and Grill C59M+H7 Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C59M+H7 Ialysos, Greece Ialysos Ixia Sports Bars No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/nightlife-in-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/nightlife-in-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Nightlife In Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Nightlife In RhodesVerified listing">Share Location Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next The island has a vibrant nightlife during the summer months.Mainly, there are three bar streets on the island , and many of night clubs . There's one rule:Wherever you like, you go in 😎 📍Orfanidou Bar Street 📍Faliraki Bar Street 📍Kolympia Bar Street And the 📍Old Townis one of the liveliest spots for nightlife! Some of the most famous clubs are located on these streets : 📍Evripidou Street 📍Menekleous Street and a personal favorite  choice because of the music they play : 📍Route bar In Rhodes Town, you’ll also find an open-air nightclub that hosts events with famous DJs. In the past,  Artbat, Steve Aoki, and Miss Monique have performed there! 📍NOR Beach House Project Noteworthy are also two clubs in the beautiful Lindos : 📍Arches Plus Open Air Club 📍Amphitheatre Night Club F63G+58 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F63G+58 Rhodes, Greece Faliraki Kolympia - Afantou Rhodes Old Town Lindos - Pefki Rhodes Town Nightlife In Rhodes No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/ronda-resto-beach-bar/index.html" source="/listing/ronda-resto-beach-bar/index.html">
    <title>RONDA - Resto | Beach-Bar -</title>
    <section name="RONDA - Resto | Beach-BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍RONDA - Resto | Beach-Bar 🌐RONDA - Resto | Beach-Bar F63F+4R Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F63F+4R Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Restaurants - Bars No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">85QW+WM Faliraki Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +1Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark 86C3+C4 Rhodes Greek Cuisine - Restaurant +2Restaurants - Bars, Traditional homemade Greek dishes Quick view Bookmark C6PQ+M4 Rhodes Restaurants - Bars Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/fellini-gelato-artigianale/index.html" source="/listing/fellini-gelato-artigianale/index.html">
    <title>Fellini Gelato Artigianale -</title>
    <section name="Fellini Gelato ArtigianaleVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Fellini Gelato Artigianale 🌐Fellini Gelato Artigianale F629+GX Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F629+GX Rhodes, Greece Ice Cream Crepes waffles Rhodes Town Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+8P Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 75R7+65 Afantou Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark 86Q3+W7 Faliraki Ice Cream - Crepes - Waffles Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/koukos-rhodian-guesthouse/index.html" source="/listing/koukos-rhodian-guesthouse/index.html">
    <title>Koukos Rhodian Guesthouse -</title>
    <section name="Koukos Rhodian GuesthouseVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Koukos Rhodian Guesthouse 🌐Koukos Rhodian Guesthouse F62C+G2 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions F62C+G2 Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Brunch Spots No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/the-cake-box/index.html" source="/listing/the-cake-box/index.html">
    <title>The Cake Box -</title>
    <section name="The Cake BoxVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍The Cake Box 🌐The Cake Box C5C5+G8 Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C5C5+G8 Ialysos, Greece Bakery Coffee Patisserie Sandwich Take Away Breakfast Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C47G+PQ Kremasti Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/pino-ke-metho-traditional-cafeteria/index.html" source="/listing/pino-ke-metho-traditional-cafeteria/index.html">
    <title>"Pino ke Metho" Traditional Cafeteria -</title>
    <section name="&quot;Pino ke Metho&quot; Traditional CafeteriaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍"Pino ke Metho" Traditional Cafeteria 🌐"Pino ke Metho" Traditional Cafeteria 837W+Q3 Ψινθος, GreeceGet Directions 837W+Q3 Ψινθος, Greece Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/salakhouri-coast-a-scenic-walk-in-rhodes/index.html" source="/listing/salakhouri-coast-a-scenic-walk-in-rhodes/index.html">
    <title>Salakhouri Coast: A Scenic Walk in Rhodes -</title>
    <section name="Salakhouri Coast: A Scenic Walk in RhodesVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next The 📍SachtouriCoastis one of the most beautiful spots for a stroll! On one side, you’ll find boats and shops lining the coast, offering plenty of choices. On the other side, the towering walls of the medieval city of Rhodes create a stunning backdrop! 🔑Tips: This area is lively at all hours of the day, so take your time and enjoy a slow-paced walk (15-20 minutes). Just before sunset, the sunlight hits the tall city walls, creating a magical view that’s perfect for photos. Top Spots for Views and Photos: Dolphin Fountain Gate of the Virgin Sea Gate Naillac Tower Ακτή Σαχτούρη, 851 31 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions Ακτή Σαχτούρη, 851 31 Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Old Town Rhodes Town Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/traditional-taverna-yiannis/index.html" source="/listing/traditional-taverna-yiannis/index.html">
    <title>traditional Taverna “Yiannis” -</title>
    <section name="traditional Taverna “Yiannis”Verified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍traditional Taverna “Yiannis” 🌐traditional Taverna “Yiannis” 96P6+FQ Koskinou, GreeceGet Directions 96P6+FQ Koskinou, Greece Koskinou Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/coffee-berry-ialysos/index.html" source="/listing/coffee-berry-ialysos/index.html">
    <title>Coffee Berry Ialysos -</title>
    <section name="Coffee Berry IalysosVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Coffee Berry Ialysos 🌐Coffee Berry Ialysos C584+GQ Ialysos, GreeceGet Directions C584+GQ Ialysos, Greece Bakery Sandwich Coffee Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/periklis-faliraki/index.html" source="/listing/periklis-faliraki/index.html">
    <title>Periklis Faliraki -</title>
    <section name="Periklis FalirakiVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Periklis Faliraki 🌐Periklis Faliraki 85QX+RQ Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 85QX+RQ Faliraki, Greece Faliraki Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/takis-sandwiches-more/index.html" source="/listing/takis-sandwiches-more/index.html">
    <title>Takis Sandwiches &amp;amp; More -</title>
    <section name="Takis Sandwiches &amp;amp; MoreVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Takis Sandwiches &amp;amp; More 🌐Takis Sandwiches &amp;amp; More C6HM+V2 Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6HM+V2 Rhodes, Greece Coffee Sandwich Take Away Breakfast Rhodes Town Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/kounna-beach-resto-bar/index.html" source="/listing/kounna-beach-resto-bar/index.html">
    <title>Kounna Beach &amp;amp; Resto Bar -</title>
    <section name="Kounna Beach &amp;amp; Resto BarVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Kounna Beach &amp;amp; Resto Bar 🌐Kounna Beach &amp;amp; Resto Bar 86C5+HG Καλλιθέα, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 86C5+HG Καλλιθέα, Ελλάδα Faliraki Brunch Spots No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/taverna-paraga/index.html" source="/listing/taverna-paraga/index.html">
    <title>Taverna Paraga -</title>
    <section name="Taverna ParagaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Taverna Paraga 🌐Taverna Paraga 7X69+CX Apollona, GreeceGet Directions 7X69+CX Apollona, Greece Middle Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 836W+WW Καλλιθέα Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/mojito-beach-bar-lahania-the-perfect-relaxation-spot/index.html" source="/listing/mojito-beach-bar-lahania-the-perfect-relaxation-spot/index.html">
    <title>Mojito Beach Bar, Lahania: The Perfect Relaxation Spot -</title>
    <section name="Mojito Beach Bar, Lahania: The Perfect Relaxation SpotVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Mojito Beach Bar in Lahania is a testament to the owner's dedication and passion and it t shows in every aspect. From the inviting atmosphere and delightful food and drinks to the warm welcome you receive. If you're a traveler seeking relaxation, this is the ideal spot for you. The beach is pristine, and the waters are always crystal clear. It's the perfect escape from the city. 📍Mojito Beach Bar 🌐Mojito Beach Bar XVCX+X3 South Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions XVCX+X3 South Rhodes, Greece No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/poseidon-beach-kallithea-tranquility-and-simple-pleasures/index.html" source="/listing/poseidon-beach-kallithea-tranquility-and-simple-pleasures/index.html">
    <title>Poseidon Beach, Kallithea: Tranquility and Simple Pleasures -</title>
    <section name="Poseidon Beach, Kallithea: Tranquility and Simple PleasuresVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next Poseidon Beach in Kallithea offers the perfect blend of peace and enjoyment. With its pristine beach, clean waters, and simple yet delicious food, it’s a haven for those who appreciate the quieter, more serene spots. As the years go by, I find myself drawn to places like this more and more. 📍Find it here:Poseidon Beach 96CH+WQ Koskinou 851 00, GreeceGet Directions 96CH+WQ Koskinou 851 00, Greece No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/discover-the-islands-hidden-gems-2/index.html" source="/listing/discover-the-islands-hidden-gems-2/index.html">
    <title>Discover the Island's Hidden Gems! -</title>
    <section name="Discover the Island's Hidden Gems!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next The best choice for organized activities on the island! You can discover hidden beaches by kayaking or explore the mountains of Rhodes through easy trails! Unforgettable experiences await! While good physical condition is generally required, there are programs suitable for everyone! 📌 Mr Local's recommendation: 📍Banana Trails 🌐Banana 📍Trekking Hellas Rhodes 🌐Trekking Hellas Rhodes 86M5+73 Faliraki, GreeceGet Directions 86M5+73 Faliraki, Greece Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/anemos-taverna/index.html" source="/listing/anemos-taverna/index.html">
    <title>Anemos Taverna -</title>
    <section name="Anemos TavernaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Anemos Taverna 🌐Anemos Taverna 64JP+GF Αρχάγγελος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 64JP+GF Αρχάγγελος, Ελλάδα Stegna - Archangelos Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark C6JP+VQ Rhodes Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/stani-bakery-pastry-shop/index.html" source="/listing/stani-bakery-pastry-shop/index.html">
    <title>Stani Bakery &amp;amp; Pastry Shop -</title>
    <section name="Stani Bakery &amp;amp; Pastry ShopVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Stani Bakery &amp;amp; Pastry Shop 📍Stani Bakery &amp;amp; Pastry Shop 📍Stani Bakery &amp;amp; Pastry Shop 🌐Stani Bakery &amp;amp; Pastry Shop C6PG+GM Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6PG+GM Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Must-Visit Patisseries No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">C6MG+PJ Rhodes Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark C47G+JG Kremasti Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark 94PP+MM Pastida Must-Visit Patisseries Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/bakis-taverna/index.html" source="/listing/bakis-taverna/index.html">
    <title>Bakis Taverna -</title>
    <section name="Bakis TavernaVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Bakis Taverna - Traditional 🌐Bakis Taverna - Traditional C6JP+VQ Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions C6JP+VQ Rhodes, Greece Rhodes Town Must-Try Tavernas - Meze No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">7XCQ+XR Κάμειρος Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 7X69+CX Apollona Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark 836W+WW Καλλιθέα Must-Try Tavernas - Meze Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/tsampis-family-bakery-cafe/index.html" source="/listing/tsampis-family-bakery-cafe/index.html">
    <title>Tsampis &amp;amp; Family Bakery Cafe -</title>
    <section name="Tsampis &amp;amp; Family Bakery CafeVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍Tsampis &amp;amp; Family Bakery Cafe 🌐Tsampis &amp;amp; Family Bakery Cafe 96XG+3W Rhodes, GreeceGet Directions 96XG+3W Rhodes, Greece Bakery Sandwich Take Away Breakfast Coffee Kallithea Grab-and-Go Breakfast No comments yet.</section>
    <section name="You May Also Be Interested In">86Q2+WJ Faliraki Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark 4374+6Q Λίνδος Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark C5C5+G8 Ialysos Grab-and-Go Breakfast Quick view Bookmark</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/akti-miaouli-kritika-ixia-ialyssos/index.html" source="/listing/akti-miaouli-kritika-ixia-ialyssos/index.html">
    <title>Akti Miaouli - Kritika - Ixia - Ialyssos -</title>
    <section name="Akti Miaouli - Kritika - Ixia - IalyssosVerified listing">Visit Profile Reviews0 prev next Website Leave a review Get directions Share prev next The western side of Rhodes, as highlighted in the photos, is a prime spot for windsurfing, kite surfing, and other water sports due to the frequent strong winds in the area. This side of the island is ideal for those seeking an active, adrenaline-filled experience on the water. However, if your goal is to relax, the constant wind can be a bit bothersome. Despite this, one undeniable advantage of this side of Rhodes is the breathtaking sunsets. The vibrant colors and stunning scenery will leave a lasting impression, making it a must-see for sunset lovers. 📍Akti Miaouli Beach 📍Akti kanari Beach 📍Ixia Beach 📍Ialysos Beach Καλύμνου 8, Ρόδος 851 00, ΕλλάδαGet Directions Καλύμνου 8, Ρόδος 851 00, Ελλάδα No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/prasonisi-prasonisi-lighthouse-2/index.html" source="/listing/prasonisi-prasonisi-lighthouse-2/index.html">
    <title>Prasonisi - Prasonisi Lighthouse -</title>
    <section name="Prasonisi - Prasonisi LighthouseVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Prasonisi is located at the southernmost tip of Rhodes, where nature has created a stunning landscape! The islet is connected to the mainland by a strip of sand, forming two exotic sandy beaches that change shape depending on the season and weather conditions. Due to favorable winds, this area is a favorite destination for kitesurfers and windsurfers from all around the world! 📍Prasonisi Beach As you pass the main beach and head towards Prasonisi, there is a hidden beach worth visiting! At the end of the islet, you'll find the famous Prasonisi Lighthouse, offering a unique and breathtaking view. 🔑Tips: Visit the hidden beach with a companion for safety.The area offers amazing views and is perfect for photography. For the best views and photos at Prasonisi, there are a few must-visit spots:📍Viewpoint for Photos 📍Stone Attraction 📍Hidden beach 📍Prasonisi Lighthouse VQRF+2R Νότια Ρόδος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions VQRF+2R Νότια Ρόδος, Ελλάδα South Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/rhodescape-park-at-apollakia-dam/index.html" source="/listing/rhodescape-park-at-apollakia-dam/index.html">
    <title>Rhodescape Park at Apollakia Dam -</title>
    <section name="Rhodescape Park at Apollakia DamVerified listing">Profile Reviews0 prev next Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share Report prev next Located by the stunning man-made lake, Rhodescape Park offers a range of exciting activities for you and your kids to enjoy! Whether you're into archery, kayaking, zip-lining, or climbing (for kids), there's something for everyone! You can also try Stand Up Paddleboarding (SUP), sea biking, and relax with a snack or coffee. For those seeking a unique aerial experience over the lake, the flying fox is a must-try. Overnight stays are also available for those who want to fully immerse themselves in nature. I highly recommend it for nature lovers, but it's also perfect for a quick coffee stop! 📍Rhodes Escape Park 🌐Rhodes Escape Park 4Q2X+VM Νότια Ρόδος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 4Q2X+VM Νότια Ρόδος, Ελλάδα Middle Rhodes South Rhodes Top Places No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/o-mponiatis/index.html" source="/listing/o-mponiatis/index.html">
    <title>O Mponiatis -</title>
    <section name="O MponiatisVerified listing">Share Location Website Profile Reviews0 prev next Location Get directions Leave a review Bookmark Share prev next 📍O Mponiatis 🌐O Mponiatis C46F+V2 Kremasti, GreeceGet Directions C46F+V2 Kremasti, Greece Kremasti Gyros Time No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/listing/rhodescape-park-at-apollakia-dam-an-adventure-for-the-whole-family-2/index.html" source="/listing/rhodescape-park-at-apollakia-dam-an-adventure-for-the-whole-family-2/index.html">
    <title>Rhodescape Park at Apollakia Dam: An Adventure for the Whole Family! -</title>
    <section name="Rhodescape Park at Apollakia Dam: An Adventure for the Whole Family!Verified listing">Visit Share Bookmark Details Reviews0 prev next Get directions prev next Located by the stunning man-made lake, Rhodescape Park offers a range of exciting activities for you and your kids to enjoy! Whether you're into archery, kayaking, zip-lining, or climbing (for kids), there's something for everyone! You can also try Stand Up Paddleboarding (SUP), sea biking, and relax with a snack or coffee. For those seeking a unique aerial experience over the lake, the flying fox is a must-try. Overnight stays are also available for those who want to fully immerse themselves in nature. I highly recommend it for nature lovers, but it's also perfect for a quick coffee stop! 📌Check it out here: 📍Rhodescape Park 🔑 Tips: Wear comfortable athletic clothing and shoes. Be cautious on the final stretch of the road. 4Q2X+PF Νότια Ρόδος, ΕλλάδαGet Directions 4Q2X+PF Νότια Ρόδος, Ελλάδα Activities No comments yet.</section>
  </document>
  <document id="/colossus-of-rhodes-history-facts-legacy-of-the-ancient-world-wonder/index.html" source="/colossus-of-rhodes-history-facts-legacy-of-the-ancient-world-wonder/index.html">
    <title>Colossus of Rhodes: History, Facts &amp;amp; Legacy of the Ancient World Wonder -</title>
    <section name="Colossus of Rhodes: History, Facts &amp;amp; Legacy of the Ancient World Wonder">Local History &amp;amp; Destinations Mar 21 Share post Rhodes, the sun-drenched jewel of the Aegean, was once home to one of the most extraordinary creations of the ancient world—theColossus of Rhodes. This massive statue, standing proudly at the entrance of the island’s harbor in the area now known as “Elafakia,” was a tribute toHelios, the Sun God. As one of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World, the Colossus symbolized the power, wealth, and resilience of the Rhodians.</section>
    <section name="A Monument to the Sun God">Unfortunately, an earthquake in226 BCEtoppled the great statue, and it was never rebuilt. However, its legend lives on, not only in history books but also in modern culture and even in the identity of Rhodes’ sports teams.</section>
    <section name="Rhodes’ Sports Teams Honoring the Sun God">Even today, the legacy of Helios shines brightly in the island’s sporting culture. Two major teams in Rhodes carry the spirit of the Sun God in their identity, proudly representing the island on the national and local levels. Sport:Basketball League:Greek A1 Basketball League Emblem:The team’s logo features the iconicColossus of Rhodes, paying homage to the island’s ancient heritage. About:Established in 1963, A.O. Kolossos Rhodes is a competitive force in Greek basketball, regularly competing in the country’s top-tier league. The team’s commitment to excellence echoes the strength and resilience of the original Colossus. Learn more Sport:Football (Soccer) League:First local football division Emblem:The club’s emblem featuresApollo, the god often associated with the sun, music, and prophecy. About:A.O. Apollon Kallithion is a well-respected football club in Rhodes, embodying the competitive spirit and energy of the island. The team’s passion for the game and deep-rooted connection to mythology make it a cherished part of the local sports scene. Follow them on Facebook</section>
    <section name="Rhodes: A Timeless Connection to the Sun">From its ancient marvels to its modern-day sports teams, Rhodes continues to celebrate its deep connection to the sun and its divine guardian, Helios. Whether through the memory of the Colossus or the passion of local athletes, the island remains a place where history and culture shine as brightly as its endless summer skies. antiquitycolossus-of-rhodeshistoryrhodes colossus-of-rhodeshistoryrhodes historyrhodes rhodes</section>
  </document>
</corpus>